<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Horror Story</string>


    <string name="first">The 7th Barn (or The Seven Barns) is a scary urban legend about a haunted barn in Ohio that is believed to have been the scene of the grisly murders of an entire family.



There was a wealthy farmer who owned a lot of land in Ohio. He built a new barn on his property every time his wife had a baby. He named the barns after each of his children and, by the time this story takes place, they had 6 kids and were expecting number seven.

However, the farmer’s wife died in childbirth and so did her unborn baby. The farmer went insane with grief and couldn’t tend to his farm. The family had no money and the farm started going under.

They say that, one night, in the depths of his madness and despair, the farmer took an axe and led his children out to the barns where he murdered them, one by one. He buried each of their bodies in the six barns that had been named after them. Then, the farmer went to the 7th barn where he hung himself.

As the story goes, all of the barns were eventually torn down and the land was sold off. All except for the 7th barn. Nobody wanted to buy the land because of what had happened there, so it was abandoned and soon fell into disrepair.



They say if you go to that barn at night you can see the ghost of the farmer hanging from the rafters, his body swinging back and forth in the wind, dwelling on his terrible crime for all eternity.

No one was ever really sure where the seventh barn was located, although it was definitely in Ohio. Some said it was the Cranz farm in Cuyahoga Valley and others said it was at Top O’ The World in Northampton.

In 1997, a local Ohio teacher claimed that, after a lot of research, he had finally managed to track down the real location of the infamous 7th Barn. He said that none of the barns had ever actually been torn down. The land had just been divided up and sold off and the barns had simply been incorporated into neighboring farms.

According to the teacher, he was able to pinpoint the correct location because all of the barns on neighboring properties had nameplates above their doors with the names of children engraved on them.

The teacher and his son set out at night to visit the barn, bringing a video camera with them, in the hopes of capturing some paranormal activity.

The next morning, the teacher’s wife reported her husband and son missing. Police found their abandoned car by the roadside. While searching the area, they entered a barn in a nearby field and found the dead bodies of the teacher and his son hanging from the rafters.</string>

    <string name="second">Black-eyed children (or Black-eyed kids) is an urban legend about strange kids with eyes that are completely black who accost people late at night and demand help. Some people believe they are evil creatures in disguise and others believe they are aliens.


The urban legend began in 1996 when a man named Brian Bethel from Abeleine, Texas claimed he had an encounter with two very strange children.

One night, he was getting into his car, which was parked outside a movie theater, when two young boys approached and knocked on his window. The man rolled down his window, but he got the strangest feeling that something wasn’t quite right.

“Hey, mister, we have a problem,” said the older boy in a calm voice. “You see, my friend and I want to see the films, but we forgot our money. We need to go to our house to get it. Want to help us out?”

There was something about the two pale boys that scared the man and he hesitated.



“C’mon, mister. Let us in. We can’t get in your car until you do, you know,” the boy said soothingly. “Just let us in, and we’ll be gone before you know it. We’ll go to our mother’s house.”

For the first time, the man noticed their eyes. They were as black as coal. There was no pupil and no iris. Just two completely black eyes.

As if sensing the man’s unease, they boy said, “Cmon, mister. We won’t hurt you. You have to LET US IN. We don’t have a gun…”

The man was frightened and threw the car into reverse.

The boy shouted, “WE CAN’T COME IN UNLESS YOU TELL US IT’S OKAY. LET! US! IN!”

The man drove off, but when he looked back, he saw that the boys were gone and the sidewalk outside the movie theater was deserted.



The story was originally posted on a website called “Obiwan’s UFO-Free Paranormal Page” and ever since then, people have been reporting encounters with similar black-eyed children.

All of the encounters seem to take place at night, when the person is alone in their home or in their car. The children’s faces are usually partially obscured by hoodies or hats and the people report a strange sense of unease or forboding. When the people notice their black eyes, the children become insistant and aggressive and when they can’t get into the house or car, they mysteriously disappear.

</string>


    <string name="third">Spring heeled jack is a scary urban legend about a mysterious creature who terrorized London in the 1830s.


Rumors about a monster named Spring-Heeled Jack began to circulate in London towards the end of 1837. Young women were being attacked by a hideous and repulsive creature who sprang out of the shadows and breathed flames from his mouth. He would assault them and scratch them with his sharp claws before disappearing into the night.

Some witnesses claimed that he had wings like a bat and horns on his head like a devil. They said he had terrible, protruding eyes and a ghoulish laugh. People gathered together and formed vigilante groups, patrolling the streets at night in an effort to catch him.

The police did not take these reports very seriously until Spring-Heeled Jack began attacking in London.

One night in February 1838, a young woman Jane Alsop was spending a quiet evening at home with her family when she heard someone knocking violently on the front door. When she opened the door, Jane saw a tall man standing in the shadows near the front gate. It was a foggy night and she couldn’t make out his face.



“I’m a police officer,” he said. “For God’s sake, bring me a light, for we have caught Spring-Heeled Jack in the lane!”

Jane ran to fetch a candle, but when she gave it to the man at the gate, he held it up to his face and she realized the terrible mistake she had made. In the dim light, she saw the hideous features of Spring-Heeled Jack himself.

As Jane screamed, the creature vomited forth a huge amount of flame from his mouth. Then, he grabbed her and tore at her clothes with his sharp claws. She tried to get away, but the man caught her and continued his attack.

Jane’s family heard her screams and they ran out into the street to help, but Spring-Heeled Jack hurried away and disappeared into the night before anyone else could get a good look at him.

Jane described her inhuman attacker to the police, saying that he wore a tight oilskin suit, and a kind of close-fitting helmet on his head

It appears wearing a helmet and a bright white suit. He attacked the girl with metal claws, tearing the dress.



A few nights later, an 18-year old girl named Lucy Scales was walking home with her sister. As they passed a dark alley, a tall cloaked figure suddenly jumped out of the shadows and attacked Lucy. He spat blue flames into her face, blinding her. As she lay writhing on the ground, Spring-Heeled Jack calmly turned around and melted back into the shadows.

When news of the attacks got out, panic spread over the city of London.

In October 1837, a girl by the name of Mary Stevens was walking home after visiting her parents. On her way through Clapham Common, a strange figure leaped out at her from a dark alley. He held her in a tight grip, completely immobilizing her and began to kiss her face. Then, he started ripping at her clothes and scratching her with his claws. She said his hands on her flesh felt as “cold and clammy as those of a corpse”. In a panic, Mary screamed and her attacker quickly fled the scene. In the commotion, several residents launched a search for the mysterious Spring-Heeled Jack, but he could not be found.

As these stories multiplied, people demanded that the police protect them. The most terrifying thing about the whole mystery was that no one knew for sure when he would strike.

As time went on, the reports of Spring-Heeled Jack’s appearances became less and less and he evolved into a figure of folklore. Authors would write stories about his exploits and the public read them with excitement.</string>

    <string name="fourth">
Dancing with the Devil is an urban legend about a girl who goes to her school dance and meets a strange man in black. It is also known as “The Devil at the Dance”.


There was a young girl who lived in Texas. She was excited because it was the night of the high school dance. She had bought a brand new dress for the occasion and she was sure she was going to look beautiful in it. She wanted the dance to be the best evening of her young life.

Then her mother came in the house, looking pale and determined.

“You are not going to that dance,” her mother said.

“But why?” the girl asked her mother.



“I’ve just been talking to the preacher. He says the dance is going to be for the devil. You are absolutely forbidden to go,” her mother said.

The girl nodded as if she accepted her mother’s words, but she was determined to go to the dance. As soon as her mother was busy, she put on her brand new dress, sneaked out of the house and hurried to her high school.

As soon as she walked into the ballroom, all of the young men turned to look at her. She was startled by all the attention. Normally, no one noticed her. Her mother sometimes accused her of being too awkward to get a boyfriend. But she was not awkward that night. The boys in her class were fighting with each other to dance with her.

Later, she broke away from the crowd and went to the table to get some punch to drink. She heard a sudden hush. The music stopped. When she turned around, she saw a handsome young man with jet black hair standing next to her. He looked striking, with jet-black hair slicked back from his forehead and an expensive suit.

“You will dance with me,” he said.

The girl managed to stammer a “yes”, completely stunned by this gorgeous man. He led her out on the dance floor. The music sprang up at once. She found herself dancing better than she had ever danced before. They were the center of attention.



Then the man spun her around and around. She gasped for breath, trying to step out of the spin. But he spun her faster and faster. Her feet felt hot. The floor seemed to melt under her. When she looked down, she noticed that the young man wasn’t wearing any shoes and instead of feet, he had black hooves.

He spun her even faster. She was spinning so fast that a cloud of dust flew up around them both so that they were hidden from the crowd.

When the dust settled, the girl was gone. The man in black bowed once to the crowd and disappeared. The devil had come to his party and he had spun the girl all the way to hell.





</string>


    <string name="fifth">






Polybius is an urban legend about a rare arcade game that caused seizures or brain aneurysms and was used in mind control experiments to brainwash people and even cause them to kill themselves.


Back in the 1980s, if people wanted to play computer games, they had to go to arcades that had stand-alone machines. The Polybius game was supposedly released in 1981 to arcades in Portland, Oregon.

The machines were completely black and the only decoration was the name Polybius in bright letters at the top. There was just a button and a joystick used for gameplay. They say it was a puzzle/shoot-em-up game, somewhat like Tempest, where you move a rotating ship around the screen and shoot to destroy the enemies.

Polybius supposedly became very popular. It was extremely addictive and people would form long lines, waiting to play it. However, there was something sinister about the game. Players reported experiencing strange things, such as hearing the sound of a woman crying and seeing grotesque faces out of the corner of their eyes. Some saw disturbing subliminal messages flashing up on the screen, saying things like, “Kill Yourself”.

After playing the game, people would have horrible nightmares, waking up in a panic. Others experienced extreme nausea, convulsions and vomiting. Others got headaches, blackouts, hallucinations or even developed amnesia. Some unlucky people even committed suicide.



According to one owner of an arcade, mysterious men in black suits would often come to collect records from the game. They did not collect any money, just data on gameplay and in some cases, they would change the settings. Because of this, the leading theory is that it was some sort of government experiment using subliminal messages to brainwash people and control their minds.

The game remains in obscurity because about one month after its release, all of the cabinets suddenly disappeared. One cabinet reappeared in an arcade 1998, but quickly disappeared again. While some have tried to recreate the game, no one has ever found the original ROM. It was supposedly created by a mysterious company called Sinneslöschen (which is German for “Sense Deletion”).

An episode of The Simpsons contained a reference to Polybius.


</string>

    <string name="sixth">The Amusement Park is a scary urban legend about an abandoned theme park in Canada, called Pennyland, that is said to be haunted by the ghost of a serial killer and his victims.


According to legend, Pennyland was one of Canada’s most popular amusement parks. During the 25 years it was open, over 200,000 people walked through its gates to enjoy its rides and amusements. However, there was a terrible accident on the ferris wheel and several people were killed. Pennyland was forced to shut down and most of the rides were dismantled. The remaining ones were abandoned and left to fall into disrepair.

Years later, police were called when a dead body was found on the grounds of the old amusement park. A vagrant had collapsed and died of a drug overdose in the toilets. Following procedure, the police made a routine search of the grounds. What they found horrified them.

In the building that housed the old ferris wheel, they discovered two rotting corpses. It was the remains of two young girls. The policeman who came across the bodies was severely traumatized and left the force soon afterwards.

One night, a teenage boy was passing by the abandoned amusement park when he noticed that some of the lights were on. Curious, he decided to investigate. As he drew closer to one of the buildings, a girl suddenly appeared at the window. There were cuts all over her face and she was covered in blood.



The teenager was about to go inside to help her when a strange man emerged from the doorway. He was carrying a bloody knife. Frightened, the boy began backing away. The crazed man rushed towards him. Suddenly, all the lights went out and the building was plunged into darkness.

Scrambling around, looking for something to use to defend himself, the boy picked up a metal pipe. Gripping it tightly, he swung around, ready to fight for his life. Just then, the lights came back on and he was shocked to discover that the man and the girl were gone. All that was left was a bloody handprint on the window.






</string>





    <string name="seventh">


The Never Ending Road is a creepy urban legend about a mysterious road in either Corona, California in the United States or in Alberta, Canada. This legend is also known as “The Lost Wreck” or “The Fatal Wreck”.


Years ago, there was a road that was known by locals as “The Never Ending Road”. Some say it was Lester Road in Corona, California and others maintain it was Miette Hot Springs Road in Alberta, Canada. It was a long, winding road, unlit and bordered by a thick forest, that led through the mountains.

According to legend, many people who drove down the road at night were never seen or heard from again. The legend of the Never Ending Road became so well-known that a lot of folks were even afraid to drive on it during the daylight hours. Some drivers would even lose their nerve and turn back, terrified that if they continued along the road, they would never return.

The road took a sharp turn at at one point and curved around a large canyon. There were no guard rails on the turn and on the other side of the canyon, the road continued.

One Summer, a work crew were widening the road when they made a gruesome discovery. One of the workmen pushed a rock over the side of the canyon and heard it hit something metal. When they climbed down to look, the workmen found dozens of crashed cars at the bottom. They had all fallen to their doom and the decomposing bodies and skeletal remains of the victims were still strapped into their seats.



It was discovered that the roads on either side of the canyon lined up so well that, when viewed from the correct angle, especially at night, it created an optical illusion. The canyon was almost invisible and the road seemed to continue on up and over the hill on the other side of the canyon. People who drove down the road at night had no idea that there was a huge drop in front of them until it was too late and they careened off the cliff and plummeted to their deaths.

They say that local law enforcement hushed up the discovery, wanting to avoid a scandal and the road was quietly closed down, never to be reopened. The corpses of the dead were never able to be recovered and they still lie there to this day, in their twisted metal graves.
</string>



    <string name="eight">
 Cucuy is a scary Mexican urban legend about a creature who kidnaps children who don’t behave themselves. He is the Mexican boogeyman.


According to Mexican folklore, El Cucuy is a small, hideous, hairy creature with glowing red eyes. He has big ears like a bat and a mouth full of razor-sharp teeth like a barracuda.

The legend has been passed down over the years by word of mouth, from mother to child. Mexican parents often warn their children, “Behave yourself or El Cucuy will come and take you away.”

When night falls, El Cucuy comes. He hides in your closet or under your bed. He can take the shape of any dark shadow. He watches you silently and waits for his moment to pounce. Then, he will take you away to his lair, deep in the mountains, and devour you.

“I grew up a in a small town in Mexico. My mother used to tell me ghost stories when I was a child, but none of them scared me as much as el cucuy. One day, I was angry and I cursed at my mother. She got very quiet and she looked at me with fury burning in her eyes. Slowly and calmly, she said, “el cucuy te va a raspar los pies en la noche” which means “El Cucuy is going to scratch your feet tonight”. Something about the way she said it really scared me. That night, I went to bed and it took me nearly two hours to fall asleep. The next morning, when I woke up, I got out of bed and noticed that my feet were sore. I looked down and saw that both of my feet had long red scratches on them. It truly terrified me because I didn’t know if el cucuy was real or if my mother was so crazy that she scratched up my feet while I was asleep to teach me a lesson.”</string>


    <string name="ninth">










The Lechuza is a scary Mexican urban legend or myth about an old woman who can turn into a giant black bird. “Lechuza” means “Owl” in English. This story is also known as “La Mujer Lechuza” which means “The Owl Witch”.


According to Mexican folklore, a Lechuza is an old witch (or Bruja) who can turn herself into a monstrous black bird. They will prey on people who they think have done them wrong or they will steal children to use in their occult rituals. Some say that the Lechuza has sold her soul to the devil in order to gain her powers.

Usually, the Lechuza will appear as a large bird, the size of a human being. It can also appear as a creature with the body of a bird but the head of a hideous old woman.

They usually only come out at dusk or after nightfall. Many people in Mexico have spotted lechuzas flying high over the tops of houses or have seen it outlined against the moon at night.

If the Lechuza fixates on you, it will sit outside your door at night, making crying sounds like a baby. If you go outside to investigate, it will swoop down on you and carry you away.



If you find unexplained scratches on your door or windowsill, it could mean a Lechuza has visited your house during the night.

“When I was a child, my family lived in a little town near the mountains in mexico. I remember my mom telling me about an old lady that lived nearby. She was 60 or 70 years old and my mom said she was suspected of being a witch and could turn into a “lechuza”. Apparently, the old woman had done some witchcraft (“brujeria”) on my grandma. My grandmother’s hair and eyebrows were gone. Some people in the town wanted to hurt the “lechuza” to see if it was really this old lady. One night, when they saw the giant black bird, they took out their guns and started shooting at it. One of them shot it in the leg. They waited and waited, but for days the old lady never left her house. When she eventually came out, she couldn’t walk and she was hobbling around on a cane…”

“My family is from Chihuahua, Mexico. My older sister claimed she saw a lechuza a few years ago when she went back to visit. They were swimming at a local pond and they saw an enormous black bird watching them from afar. They started getting freaked out and decided to go home. The lechuza followed them all the way home while they were driving and stayed outside their house until dawn. My uncles claimed they shot a lechuza and the next morning, they found an old lady lying there dead from gunshot wounds… so… either lechuzas are real… or…my uncles are murderers!”</string>


    <string name="tenth">






The Video Tape is a scary urban legend about a cursed VHS video cassette. It is said that if you watch the tape, you will die within 48 hours. They say that the cursed video tape in the movie, The Ring was based on this urban legend.


Years ago, there was a group of three girls who went to high school together. They were all best friends and one night, during the Summer holidays, they decided to have a sleepover party.

They spent all day planning their sleepover and, because they were all horror fans, they decided to rent a scary movie. It was late at night when the three girls piled into a car and drove down to their local video rental store, but it was closed. The girls spent the next half hour driving around town, looking for a video store that was still open.

Eventually, they found a little shop that was located in a side street and went inside. The girls could not agree on a film to rent, so one of them went over to the woman behind the counter and asked her if she had any suggestions. The woman told her that she had just the thing for them and disappeared into a back room.

While they were waiting, one of the girls noticed a video tape lying on the counter. It didn’t have a box cover or a label and it seemed to be very dirty and stained. She was curious to see what it was and reached out to pick it up.



Just then, the woman came rushing out from the back room and slammed her hand down on the tape, pulling it away.

With a stange smile on her face, she said, “That’s not something you girls should be watching.”

When they asked her what it was, the woman told them not to touch it and all would say was that it was a home movie. Then, she handed them an old horror film and told them it would be much a better movie for them to watch.

Eventually, the girls agreed to rent the tape that the woman suggested. While she was in the back room, searching for the film, one of the girls took the opportunity two swipe the mysterious video tape and stuffed it into her purse.

Later that night, when the girls returned home, the girl who stole the video tape took it out of her purse and convinced the other two that they should watch it.

They put the tape in the video recorder and pressed Play. All of a sudden, the power went out and the room was plunged into darkness. However, the television was still on.



With a crackle of static, the video started playing and, on the screen, they saw a woman tied to a wooden stake. She was surrounded by angry men and women who were carrying burning torches. They were shouting and spitting on her and then they set fire to the wood beneath the woman’s feet.

The woman began laughing maniacally and the people yelled out things like “Burn the witch!” and “This is your punishment for practicing black magic!” As the flames rose higher and higher, licking at the woman’s face, she screamed out a curse, saying that all who witness her death will suffer the same fate in two days time.

There was a screech of static and the VCR began making skipping sounds before it suddenly cut off. The terrified girls sat in the dark for a long time until the power came back on. They tried to convince each other that it must have been some type of prank. After a while, they agreed that they should return the tape immediately.

When they arrived at the location of the video store, it was gone. All they found was an abandoned building and an empty lot.

Two days later, all three of the girls were dead. The first girl was found floating in a swimming pool. Her body was burned beyond recognition. The charred remains of the second girl were discovered in the middle of a park and the third girl’s body was found in a furnace.

When the police were investigating the mysterious deaths, they thought it was a very strange coincidence that all three girls had burned to death on the same day. In each case, the police thought it had been spontaneous combustion, but the weirdest thing about it was that nothing around them had even bee.
</string>

    <string name="t11">






The Crying Baby is an urban myth that has been circulating by e-mail since 2003. It told the story of a woman who was home alone one night and heard the sound of a baby crying outside her front door.


A few years ago, an e-mail did the rounds warning people about a cunning serial killer who used a terrifying trick to lure his victims out of the safety of their homes and into his clutches.

One night, a middle-aged woman was sitting at home, reading the newspaper. Her husband worked nights which meant that she was often alone in the house.

It was getting late and she was about to go to bed, when she heard a strange noise outside. It sounded like a crying baby and seemed to be coming from the bushes outside her front door.

She thought it was very weird, but was tempted to go out and investigate. Just then, her dog jumped to its feet and began barking and growling at the door. The woman got a strange and uneasy feeling. She stopped in her tracks and decided to call the police instead.



When she told them she had heard the sound of a crying baby, the police said, “We’ll be right over. Whatever you do, DO NOT open your door.”

The lady hung up the phone and, minutes later, she heard the sound of sirens as two police cars pulled into her driveway. One policeman banged on her door, while the others searched the bushes outside her house.

The woman opened her front door and let the policeman in. He was holding a doll in his arms and she noticed that it had a tape recorder in its belly. The policeman pressed Play on the tape recorder and they both heard the sound of a baby crying.

He explained that there was a serial killer on the loose who was targeting women who were alone at night. He was using a cunning trick to fool the women into opening their front doors and coming outside. He would hide in the bushes and play a tape of a baby crying.

The recording of the baby’s cries would make the women think there was a child in need of help and they would come out of their homes. While they were looking for the source of the cries, the killer would emerge from the bushes and murder them.

He said that in the past few days, they had received several calls from women saying that they heard a crying baby outside their homes when they were alone at night. The serial killer had already murdered two women in Baton Rouge, Louisiana and if it hadn’t been for her dog warning her of the danger, she might have become his next victim.



While the police have never actually come across a real-life case like this, the e-mail was inspired by an episode of America’s Most Wanted that theorized that a serial killer in Louisiana may have been using the crying baby lure to fool one of his victims. Years later, an episode of Criminal Minds also mentioned a serial killer using the crying baby lure.


</string>


    <string name="t12">



Charlie Noonan is an urban myth about the mysterious disappearance of a man. This tale is not a true story but the image is interesting and grabs your attention. We are still looking for the origin of this creepy photo and the story behind it.


The urban legend of Charlie Noonan:

“Charlie Noonan was an amateur folklorist who travelled throughout the South and Southwestern United States during the early years of the 20th century, collecting tall tales and stories of the supernatural. According to his wife, Ellie, Charlie was told a story one day by an Oklahoma farmer about a strange woman who lived alone on an isolated property in the panhandle. The farmer claimed the woman was not a woman at all, but something else, something that hid its true nature beneath a headscarf and was never seen without a large dog by its side. Noonan was apparently intrigued enough to try searching for the woman during one of his research road trips. He was never seen again.”

“Ellie Noonan was later contacted by a Tulsa pawnbroker who remembered reading about her husband’s disappearance in the papers, after finding his name engraved on a camera sold to him by an itinerant. The pawnbroker returned the camera, and Mrs Noonan had the film inside developed in the hopes of finding a clue as to his whereabouts. This was the only photo on the roll. Unfortunately, neither the location of the property, nor the name of the farmer who told him the story was recorded in Noonan’s notes.”

However, further research reveals that this is just an urban myth. There is no folklorist named Charlie Noonan and there is no record of any of these strange events. This is just an intriguing story made up by someone on the internet, inspired by the creepy photo above.


</string>

</resources>
