<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ScrollView xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:background="@android:color/black"
    android:orientation="vertical">

    <LinearLayout
        android:layout_width="match_parent"
        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
        android:orientation="vertical">

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/barn" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="7TH BARN"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="first"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/blackeyedchildren" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="BLACK-EYED-CHILDREN"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"

            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="2nd"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/springheeledjack" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="SPRING HEELED JACK"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="third"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/dancedevil" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="DANCING WITH THE DEVIL"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="fourth"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/polybius" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="POLYBIUS"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="fifth"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/amusemen" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="THE AMUSEMENT PARK"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="sixth"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/neverendingroad" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="NEVER ENDING ROAD"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="seventh"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/elcucuy" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="EL CUCUY"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="eight
"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/lechuza" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="LECHUZA"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="ninth"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/videotape" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="THE VIDEO TAPE"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="ninth"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/cryingbaby" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="CRYING BABY"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="tenth"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/charlienoonan" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="CHARLIE NOONAN"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text=""
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/busdriver" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="BUS DRIVER"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="
Bus Driver Loses Mental Patients is a scary urban legend about a man who works for the local insane asylum and ends up accidentally allowing the inmates to escape. It is also known as “Bus Full of Mental Patients”.


There was a bus driver who worked for the county hospital. One day, he was transporting 20 mental patients to the state insane asylum. On the way, he got thirsty and decided to stop for a few drinks at a bar.

When he got back to his bus, he was shocked to find it empty. The mental patients had somehow managed to get free and all of them had escaped. Worried that he would lose his job, the crafty bus driver came up with an idea.

He drove the bus down the road and pulled over at the first bus stop he found. He opened the doors and all of people waiting there got on the bus. The bus driver took them to the insane asylum and told the staff that these patients were especially violent and had to be restrained.

It took many months before the staff of the insane asylum realized their mistake. By that time, many of the people had actually gone insane. The real mental patients have still not been found.


"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/lincolns" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="LINCOLNS"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="






The tale of The Lincolns a scary story of mutants, horrors, curses, murder and mysterious deaths. It sounds like an unbelieveable story, but it is supposed to have actually happened over 100 years ago in West Virginia, USA. Is this a true story or an urban legend? Nobody knows for sure.


In the 1890s, a family of odd-looking people moved into a small midwestern town in West Virginia. They called themselves The Lincolns. The entire family – father, mother, daughter and two sons – were squat and ugly with pallid, greenish skin, bulging eyes and wide, bulbous heads. Everyone who saw them thought they looked almost toad-like.

They were sullen and unfriendly, refusing to make friends with the townsfolk and keeping mostly to themselves. During the day, they stayed indoors, but at night, they would prowl around the town, lurking in the shadows and scaring the townsfolk.

Around 1900, one of the Lincoln sons attacked the daughter of a prominent local family and ended up killing the poor young girl. The townsfolk were so enraged and they didn’t wait for a trial. They decided to take the law into their own hands. An angry mob dragged the boy out to a lonely field and hung him by the neck from the high branches of a tree until he was dead.

At the girl’s funeral, the Lincoln family turned up seething with rage. The father put a curse on the town, and threw a worm at the dead girl’s parents, crying “Here is your doom!”



A little while later the dead girl’s father and mother were found dead under mysterious circumstances. Their bodies had been crushed to a pulp and they were covered with slime. Nobody could understand what had happened to them, but everyone suspected the Lincolns had something to do with it.

After that, some people claimed they saw the dead Lincoln boy around town. At night, there were many sightings of his ghostly apparition wandering the empty streets. Many people who saw him later went insane. There were rumors that the Lincoln boy wasn’t really dead at all.

A group of townsfolk went to the cemetery one night and were shocked to discover a trail of footprints leaving the Lincoln boy’s grave. When they dug it up and opened his coffin, they found that the boy’s corpse was gone.

The next day, the other members of the Lincoln family picked up and moved out of town. Nobody knew where they went.

For the next few years, however, the area suffered a succession of severe droughts, floods and tornadoes, almost as if the town had been cursed by the Lincolns.


"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/buckleyfamily" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="BUCKLEY FAMILY"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="The Buckley Family story is an urban myth about an old photo of two children who murdered their mother one Halloween. It is not a true story and the picture is not real.


“This is the Buckley Family. The children’s names were Susan and John. As a Halloween joke, the kids in the neighborhood were going to get a dummy and pretend to chop its head off. The Buckley children thought it would be hilarious to actually kill their mother, so when the kids walked up the door they got an axe and slaughtered her. Once everyone figured out what they had done, they called the police, but the kids were long gone by then. The only picture of them was this photo, taken by a trick or treater. The mother’s body was found half eaten.”

This photograph has been posted on various sites on the Internet with the accompanying text, but it is not true. Here is the real story:

This image is actually called “Midwestern Matricide” and it is the work of Eddie Allen from Haunted Memories. He retouches old photos and gives them a horrifying twist. In this case, he took a normal photo of two children and their mother and made it look like they had murdered her. If you look at the original photograph below, you will see that the mother’s head is still on her shoulders and the daughter isn’t holding an axe.
"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/clapclap" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="CLAP CLAP"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="




Clap Clap is a scary story about a man and woman who get lost in the mountains and come across an old cabin.

One day, a young married couple went hiking in the mountains. As the sun began to set, they realized that they were lost. The wife was getting worried, but her husband tried to calm her down and assured her that they would eventually find their way back to their car. However, after walking for hours, they still had no idea where they were.

It was growing dark and the man and wife were getting desperate. They didn’t have a map or a compass with them and all of the trees looked the same. Just when they were about to give up hope, they came across an old cabin in a clearing.

The cabin looked as if it had seen better days. It was dilapidated and seemed like it hadn’t been used in a long time. Some of the windows were cracked and broken and a lot of the tiles had fallen off the roof. The husband knocked on the front door but there was no response. When he turned the handle, it slowly creaked open.

Inside, they found it was in a bad state of disrepair. There was very little furniture and the floor was covered in a thick layer of dust. As the couple cautiously looked around, they noticed a strange atmosphere and a peculiar musty smell.

The walls were covered from floor to ceiling with graffiti. Written in red paint, the words, “Death! Death! Death! Death! Death!” were repeated over and over again.

The man and woman were unnerved. With a shaking hand, the husband reached out to touch the wall. He was horrified to find that the paint was not yet dry.

The couple were very frightened, but they had nowhere else to go. They knew that the mountain was dangerous at night and there were lots of wild animals prowling the woods. Despite the creepy writing on the walls, they decided to stay the night.

Going upstairs, they found a moth-eaten mattress that was covered in stains. The husband and wife wrapped themselves in an old piece of carpet to keep warm and tried to make themselves as comfortable as possible under the circumstances. They lay down together on the mattress and eventually managed to fall asleep.

Sometime after midnight, the couple were awakened by a strange rustling noise. It sounded like someone or something was moving around outside the shack.

“Did you hear that?” asked his wife. “I think there’s somebody out there.”

Her husband listened for a while, but he didn’t hear anything. He got out of bed and walked over to the window. It was too dark outside to see anything. Opening the window, he stuck his head out.

“Who’s there?” he called nervously.

There was no answer.

He was about to go back to bed when his wife said, “Maybe it’s someone who can’t speak…”

The husband returned to the window and said, “Is there anybody out there? Clap once for YES and twice for NO.”

He strained his ears to listen. The stars twinkled in the night sky. The crickets were chirping loudly.

All of a sudden, he heard a loud CLAP!

The man turned to his wife and said in surprise, “You were right. There’s someone out there.”

He leaned out the window and his eyes scanned the darkness. He couldn’t make out anything in the pitch black.

“Are you the owner of this cabin?” he asked.

CLAP! CLAP!

“Are you a man?”

CLAP! CLAP!

“You’re a woman, then?”

CLAP! CLAP!

“Are you human?”

CLAP! CLAP!

A chill ran down his spine. He swallowed hard and croaked, “Did you come here alone?”

CLAP! CLAP!

“How many are with you? Clap once for each person…”
CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP! CLAP!…



"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/cellphone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="THE CELL PHONE"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="






The Cell Phone is a short, scary horror story about a woman who notices something disturbing on her mobile after she allows her young son plays with it.

There was a woman who had a six-year old son. One day, she bought a new mobile phone. When she came home from work, she started cooking dinner and left her phone down on the kitchen table.

Her son came into the kitchen and saw the phone. He asked his mother if he could play with it. She told him that he could, as long as he did not call anyone or delete any text messages. Of course, the boy agreed and went off to his bedroom to play with the phone.

Around 10PM that night, she went upstairs to tuck in her son and found him fast asleep on his bed. The new cell phone was lying on the ground beside the bed. She picked it up and began browsing though the settings to make sure he had not deleted anything. She noticed some minor changes. He had changed the theme, the background and gave her a new ringtone.

She noticed that he had taken some pictures with the cell phone. She opened the images folder and browsed through them. “How cute,” she thought. He had been taking pictures of himself.

Then she came across the last photo in the folder. When she first saw it, she couldn’t quite believe it. Were her eyes playing tricks on her? It was a photograph of her son, lying asleep on her bed. But the disturbing thing was what was lurking in the far left corner of the picture.

￼

It seemed to show the left side of a grotesque old woman’s face.
"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/knockknock" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="KNOCK KNOCK"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="



Knock Knock is a scary story about a young boy and his sister who are left home alone when their parents go out for the night. It is based on an urban legend.



As their mother was leaving, she they told her children not to open the door under any circumstances.

“If anyone knocks, don’t answer it,” she told them.

But the boy and his sister didn’t pay attention to their mother’s warning. They thought she was being too careful. They figured they could take care of themselves in any situation.

About an hour after the parents left, the kids heard a “knock, knock, knock” on the front door. They decided to ignore it, but again, they heard “knock, knock, knock”. It happened again and again and it grew louder each time.

Eventually, the girl couldn’t stand it anymore and she told her brother she was going to answer the door. When the boy reminded her of their mother’s warning, the girl just wouldn’t listen.

Again, they heard the “knock, knock, knock” on the door. Finally the sister went downstairs. Her brother lay on the sofa watcing TV. He heard his sister’s footsteps walking down the stairs. He heard her asking loudly “Who is it?”. He heard her open the lock on the front door.

Then he heard only silence. He lay there for a while, listening for any noise, but heard nothing. Eventually, he started getting scared. His sister still hadn’t returned. He was afraid to call out to his sister, so he sneaked out the back door and made his way to their neighbor’s house.

When he went into their house, his neighbor was watching the local news channel on TV. The news anchor on TV was talking about a murder. Then they showed a reporter live at the scene of the murder.

The neighbor said to the boy, “Hey that looks like your house”.

The boy was shaking with fear. “That is my house”, he said. “And that’s my front door”.




"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/carkeys" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="CAR KEYS"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="








The Car Keys is a scary story about a girl and her father who get into a car crash, one rainy night.

One night, a father and his daughter were driving down a deserted country road. They were returning home after spending the entire day visiting the girl’s mother in hospital. Listening to the sound of the rain drumming on the car roof, the girl began to doze off.

Suddenly, there was a loud bang. The father struggled with the steering wheel but the car skidded off the wet road and slammed into a stone wall.

After checking that his daughter was uninjured, the man got out of the car to survey the damage. Both of the front tires had large punctures and the right fender was crumpled against the wall. The rest of the car had survived unscathed.

“We must have driven over something on the road,” he explained to his daughter. “Whatever it was, it blew out both of the tires.”

“You can fix it, right?” asked his daughter, somewhat shaken by the accident.

“No,” replied her father, shaking his head. “I’ve only got one spare in the boot. I’ll have to walk back into town and find somebody to tow the car,” he said. “It isn’t that far from here. You wait in the car while I’m gone.”

“OK,” she said, reluctantly. “But please don’t take too long.”

The man could see in his daughter’s eyes that she was frightened.

“Sit tight,” replied her father as he he slammed the car door. “I’ll be back as soon as possible.”

His daughter watched him in the rear-view mirror as he trudged off down the road in the pouring rain and disappeared into the night.

More than an hour passed and her father stil had not returned. The girl began to wonder what was taking him so long. She was very worried because he should have been back by now.

Just then, she glanced in the rear-view mirror and saw a figure in the distance, walking towards the car. At first, she thought it was her father, but when she turned around to take a closer look, she realized that it was a strange man. He was dressed in overalls and had a big bushy beard. He was carrying something large in his left hand, swinging it back and forth.

Something about him made her very nervous. As he approached, she stared out the back window and squinted her eyes. In the dim light, she could just make out what he was clutching in his right hand. It was a big, sharp butcher’s knife.

Thinking quickly, the terrified girl locked both doors in the front of the car, then jumped into the back seat and locked the rear doors. When she looked up again, she saw that the strange man had stopped in his tracks and seemed to be staring directly at her.

Suddenly, the man raised his arm and the girl let out a blood-curdling scream. In his left hand, he was clutching her father’s severed head.

She just kept screaming and screaming. She couldn’t stop herself. Her heart was pounding and she struggled to breathe. The grotesque expression on her father’s face was horrifying to behold. His mouth was hanging open and his eyes were rolled back in his head.

When the man reached the car, he shoved his face right up against the window and glowered at her with his crazed, bloodshot eyes. His hair was wild and matted with dirt. His face was covered in deep scars.

For a moment, he just stood there, in the driving rain, grinning at her like a madman. Then, he reached into his pocket, took something out and slowly lifted his left hand.

He was holding her father’s car keys.




"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/antiquedoll" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="ANTIQUE DOLL"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="




The Antique Doll is a scary story about a young girl who receives a strange gift on her birthday.


On the morning of her birthday, Lucy’s mother woke her up and told her a package had arrived in the mail and it was addressed to her.

The girl hurriedly unwrapped the gift and was horrified at what she found inside. It was the most disgusting old doll she had ever seen. It was completely bald and it’s skin was cracked and caked in dirt. The worst thing of all was it’s teeth. They were long, pointy, sharp and beastly. They looked like an animal’s fangs.

With a shiver, she took the doll and threw it in a corner. Her mother scolded her, telling her that someone had gone to a lot of trouble to send her this antique doll. Her mother told her she had better appreciate it.

Lucy tried to protest but her mother would not listen. She forced the young girl to keep the doll. So, to put her mind at rest Lucy stuffed the antique doll into the little cupboard under the stairs, behind a pile of shoes where she wouldn’t have to look at the ugly, evil little thing.

It was not until a few nights later, when Lucy was lying in bed that she heard a noise…a shuffling sound, which went on for about five minutes. Then, a brief dragging noise and finally, a scuttling like light footsteps walking very fast.

By now Lucy was shaking in her bed with fear, unable to move. Then, she thought she heard a faint raspy voice whispering quietly from downstairs. Lucy always slept with the door open and the landing light on, as she was a little scared of the dark.

She heard the voice say “Lucy, I’m on the first step”…And then loud scrabbling again as whatever was speaking apparently turned tail and returned to it’s place of hiding.

Lucy was so scared that she didn’t sleep a wink that night but laid in fear until the break of dawn, when her mother got her up for school

Lucy tried to explain to her mother what had happened the night before, but was so tired that, when her mother passed it off as “just a dream” she began to believe it might be the case.

Of course it wasn’t. Lucy begged her parents to let her throw the antique doll in the garbage, but they insisted that it was a present and she had to keep it. So Lucy reluctantly went back to bed, telling herself that it had only been a dream. She checked the cupboard under the stairs, but the doll was exactly where Lucy had left her.

That night, Lucy fought sleep but she eventually drifted off even though she had fought sleep. Presently, the deep disembodied voice woke Lucy again. She wondered if she could only hear it in her head.

“Luuuuccccyyyy! I’m on the fourth step…”, it said. Then came to scuffling noise and the voice didn’t reoccur that night. Lucy was crying by now, and again she didn’t sleep that night. At school, Lucy told her friends about the doll, and of course they laughed at her. Lucy could only think that if the doll was climbing four steps at a time then there was only one more night to go.

That night Lucy decided to shut her bedroom door. When her mother turned her light out she asked why Lucy was no longer scared of the dark. Lucy replied that she was and could she leave her light on instead of the hall light? But her mother pointed out that her bedroom light was so bright it would keep her awake, and said no.

Therefore Lucy agreed to just sleep without a light. She opened the bedroom curtains instead to light the room a little anyway. Just as she began to doze, she heard the noise.

And then the voice came, very clear this time. “Luuuuccccyyyy! I’m on the top step…”

In the darkness of her bedroom, Lucy heard a click and trembled with fear. She wasn’t sure, but she thought she could see her bedroom door opening very, very slowly.

The next morning, Lucy’s parents found her body at the bottom of the stairs. They guessed that she had been on her way to the toilet during the night and in the darkness, had slipped and fallen down the stairs, breaking her neck.

The antique doll was found beside her body, and was buried with Lucy. Everyone said what a tragedy it was.

“She loved that doll”, said her mother. “Now they can be together forever”.
"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/reddeath" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="THE RED DEATH"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="










The Red Death is a scary story about a prince who hides in his castle while a terrible plague sweeps across the land. It is based on a classic short story by Edgar Allan Poe called “The Masque of the Red Death”.

￼

There was a prince named Prospero who lived in a huge castle in the mountains. His servants and courtiers attended to his every whim. The castle had high stone walls and was surrounded by a deep moat. At the entrance, there were were giant iron gates and an enormous portcullis over the door.

The prince heard rumors that there was a terrible plague sweeping across the land. They called it the Red Death. The disease was highly contagious and whole towns had been wiped out in a single night.

Those who were infected suffered from sudden dizziness and sharp pains and their skin broke out in a red rash. Then, within minutes, blood would start pouring from their eyes, their nose and their mouth until they collapsed, writhing around in unbearable pain and died.

As the plague drew nearer, the prince invited a hundred of his friends to take refuge in his castle and keep him company. He locked the gates, barred the windows and lowered the portcullis to keep everyone else out. Inside, the prince and his guests laughed and danced and made merry while outside the walls, the poor people suffered and died as the Red Death raged on.

To keep his guests entertained, Prince Prospero decided to hold a masquerade ball. He ordered his servants to redecorate seven rooms, especially for the ball. The first room was painted blue, from floor to ceiling. The second was pink, the third was green, the fourth was orange, the fifth was white and the sixth was purple.

The seventh room was completely black. The walls and ceiling were painted black. The carpet on the floor was black. The curtains that hung from the walls were made of black satin. All of the furniture was upholstered in black velvet.

On one of the walls, there was a large black clock with a pendulum that swung slowly to and fro, making a loud and monotonous ticking sound. Every hour, the clock would strike, giving a series of loud clangs, like the tolling of a bell.

None of the rooms had any lights. In each room, the only illumination came from a blazing fire in the fireplace that cast flickering shadows across all the walls. In the seventh room, the firelight cast such strange and frightening shadows on the walls that very few of the guests were brave enough to set foot inside it.

The masquerade ball began in the blue room and the guests were all having fun. Everyone was wearing a mask. The musicians played merry songs while the guests danced. They ate the food and drank the wine that had been laid out on the tables for them.

Whenever the clock struck the hour, the musicians would stop playing, the guests would stop dancing and everyone would stand and listen to the dull clanging chime. When the echo of the tolling bell had died away, the guests would move on to the next room and the revelry would begin again.

As the night wore on, they moved from the blue room to the pink room, to the green room, to the orange room, to the white room and to the purple room until they found themselves entering the black room.

At midnight, the clock began to strike twelve and everyone stopped to listen. As the chimes subsided, the guests became aware of a masked figure standing in the middle of them room. None of the guests had noticed him before.

The stranger was tall and gaunt. He was dressed in a dark red cape and his face was covered by a red mask in the shape of a skull.

When Prince Prospero caught sight of the figure standing among the guests, he shuddered with anger.

“Who are you?” he demanded hoarsely. “How dare you insult me by coming here without an invitation! Leave my castle this minute or I will have you killed!”

The masked figure made no move to leave. Instead, he stood there, staring at the prince. Just then, an unearthly red light illuminated the black room and the guests became so frightened that they were shaking in their boots.

Prince Propsero did not like to be disobeyed. He drew his sword and held it up. “Leave now or I shall slay you myself,” he shouted.

The masked figure slowly walked towards the prince and all of the guests drew back, too afraid to stop him. Standing in front of Prince Prospero, the figure reached up with bony hands and took off his mask.

The prince let out a sharp cry and dropped his sword. The guests screamed in horror. Behind the mask, there was no face at all, just an empty black void.

All of a sudden, Prince Prospero grew dizzy and he felt sharp pains in his sides. His skin broke out into a red rash and blood started pouring from his eyes, his nose and his mouth. His guests collapsed around him, writhing in agony and their screams echoed through the seven rooms.

The Red Death had come like a thief in the night and one by one, the prince and his guests succumbed to the terrible disease. The clock stopped ticking, the fires went out and darkness and decay and the Red Death triumphed over all.
"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/brassvase" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="THE BRASS VASE"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="






The Brass Vase is a scary story about a guy who gets a strange letter from his friend, asking him to do her a very special favor. It’s based on a story written by thoughtpod.

￼

A few days ago, I received a very strange letter from my best friend, Julia.

“Jason, I need you to do something for me tonight. It’s very, very important that you do it exactly as I ask. You’re probably going to think that this is all crazy, but please just humor me. Maybe we can laugh about all this, if I ever come back.

Do you remember the brass vase that I found half-buried in the forest? The one with the odd markings engraved on it? I need you to go to my apartment and get it.

First, I need you to get a black marker and draw two eyes on the palms of your hands. Make sure the pupils are in the middle of each palm.

Then I need you to go to my apartment. Bring a bag and a candle with you. When you get to the apartment, it will be dark. Don’t turn the lights on. Use the candle to light your way.

When you enter my bedroom, you may hear a the sound of whispering. You won’t know where it’s coming from. Don’t let it freak you out. Just ignore it. Don’t let it convince you of anything. Just remember, everything it says is a lie.

You’ll find the brass vase sitting on the dresser. Make sure you pick it up with both hands at once. Make sure the eyes on both your palms are touching the brass. If you feel something touching you, just ignore it. None of it can hurt you.

Tip the brass vase over, until all the blood has drained out. Make sure you drain it until there is not even one drop left in it. Whatever you do, don’t look inside it. For God’s sake, don’t put your fingers inside it. Just drop it into the bag and leave.

Take it away and get rid of it. Put it somewhere no one will ever find it.

I’m sorry I have to ask you to do this, Jason, but you’re the only person I can trust. If I’d known then what I know now, none of this would ever have happened.

If everything goes well, I’ll see you soon.

All my love, Julia.”

It was signed in her usual flourish. I didn’t know quite what to make of it. Was she joking? Was it some sort of prank? I decided to call her and find out. Her phone rang a dozen times, but there was no answer. Then her answering machine kicked in.

“Julia here,” the recorded voice said. “Please leave a message.”

“Hi Julia,” I said after the beep. “I know it’s late, but could you give me a call? That letter you sent kind of creeped me out and I just wanted to check that you were OK.”

I heard a faint, muffled, “Help me.”

I froze and almost dropped my cell phone.

“Julia?” I yelled. “Is that you? What’s wrong?”

“Help me,” she said again, her voice barely above a whisper. The buzzing on the line had grown louder. “frightened I’m frightened I’m frightened I’m frightened I’m frightened I’m” The buzzing was drowning out her voice completely.

“Julia,” I yelled. “What happened?”

The line went dead and I stared at my phone, her words echoing in my head.

I tried to call her back, but the line was busy. I found a candle and a bag, grabbed my car keys and left the house. I kept trying to call her all the way over to her apartment, but there was no answer.

I parked outside and when I got to the door of her apartment, I put the key in the lock and opened it. Inside, it was as dark as dark could be. I reached in and was about to flick the light switch, when I remembered the instructions in the letter.

Don’t turn on the lights.

I took out the candle instead and, after lighting it, I walked into the apartment. The flickering flame cast weird shadows on the walls.

“Julia?” I whispered.

There was a musty smell in the air. Something felt wrong and the closer I came to Julia’s bedroom, the more wrong it felt. I put my hand on the knob and opened the door.

That’s when the whispering started. It was faint and it sounded like many voices, all whispering in unison. I couldn’t make out what they were saying.

lights turn on the lights turn on the lights turn on the

It was very dark.

lights turn on the lights turn on the lights turn on the

I had to resist the urge to turn on the lights.

lights turn on the lights turn on the lights turn on the

It was very hard to resist.

The brass vase was sitting on the dresser, just as Julia said it would be. It had a squat body with a long, thin neck and an opening just large enough for two fingers to fit in.

I grabbed it carefully with both hands at once. It felt warm to the touch.

All of a sudden, the candle flickered and went out. I was plunged into darkness. It was pitch black. The whispering grew louder and louder.

That was when I remembered the instructions Julia had given me in her letter. The eyes on the palms of my hands. I had forgotten to draw them.

“There’s nothing I can do about it now,” I thought.

I tilted the vase and in the darkness, I could hear the spilling out on the floor. The room filled with the stench of copper.

I don’t know how long I stood there. Perhaps a minute. Maybe even an hour. I listened to the drip, drip, drip, and when it stopped, so did the whispering.

It was deathly quiet. All of a sudden, I realized how frightened I was. A wave of maddening fear washed over me and I just wanted to be sick. I had never been so terrified in all my life.

Dropping the vase into my bag, I left the apartment as fast as possible and went back to my car. I took out my cell phone and with shaking hands, I called Julia again. There was no answer.

All of a sudden, I felt a strange tingling in the palms of my hands. Then the whispering started again. It was all around me, surrounding me, going down on me.

I was driving towards the bridge, intent on throwing the brass vase over the side and getting rid of it that way. The whispering told me not to. It told me to turn around and go home. I obeyed. I took the brass vase home.

Each time it starts, it starts like this. First, there’s whispering. Sometimes it’s many voices at once. Sometimes it’s only one. Sometimes it sounds like my mother. Sometimes it sounds like Julia.

I always understand what they are saying.

Sometimes, they say, “feed us feed us feed us feed us feed us”

Sometimes, they say, “turn on the lights turn on the lights turn on the lights”

Sometimes they say other things… things I don’t want to repeat.

The whispering gets louder and louder and I find myself powerless to resist.

I prick my finger with a knife and hold it over the vase, squeezing the blood into its gaping mouth. This is how it feeds.

I’m a prisoner of the brass vase now. Day and night, I keep must it filled to the brim. I’m weaker than I’ve ever been in my life, but I can’t let it get hungry. It doesn’t like it when it’s hungry.

Maybe I’m just going mad. Maybe my mind has snapped. But that means I’m not insane, doesn’t it? I mean only a lunatic would consider himself sane. If you were sane enough to question your sanity, then you wouldn’t be insane any more, would you?

The whispering has started again. The vase is almost full now. Maybe this time the blood will satisfy it. Maybe this time it won’t demand any more.

I made one fatal mistake. I forgot to draw the eyes on the palms of my hands.

Julia, if you read this, I need to tell you something. I’m glad you’re free now. I’m sorry I failed to follow your instructions. If I ever manage to escape, I’ll find you, wherever you are and maybe we can have a big laugh about how crazy all of this is.

"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/earwig" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="THE EARWIGS"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="










The Earwig is a scary story about a man who puts a creepy crawly in another man’s ear. It is based on an old episode of the TV series Night Gallery, which in turn is based on an old horror story by Oscar Cook called “Boomerang”.

￼

Many years ago, in Borneo, there was an English man named Clifford Macy who was young, handsome and very vain. He fancied himself as God’s gift to women and often boasted about his success.

Macy was part owner of a tobacco plantation and his friend and business partner was another English man by the name of Leopold Warwick. Despite being old and fat, Warwick had a wife who was very young and very beautiful and she was the envy of every man who set eyes on her.

The three of them lived together in a big house on the plantation. Macy slept in the first bedroom, while Warwick and his wife slept in the second.

It was rainy season and there was precious little to do. Macy was bored and he could find nothing that would keep him entertained. As time went on, he developed a passion for Warwick’s wife and began to wish that he could have her for himself.

He tried flirting with her, but she wouldn’t have anything to do with him. One evening, when her husband was away, Macy made a pass at her, but she slapped his face.

However, Macy was the kind of man who didn’t take no for an answer. Every time she rebuffed him, he became more and more obsessed with her until he was determined to have her at any cost.

Although his heart was burning with a white hot passion, Macy had a devilish and cunning mind. He soon came up with a way to get Warwick out of the

In Borneo, there is a type of earwig that lives on waxy secretions. It has a special liking for the human ear. It’s so small and light that it could be crawling on your face and you’d barely even feel it. If it gets into a man’s ear, it creeps down the canal, unable to turn around, feeding as it goes and causing weeks of hellish torment until… well, I’m sure you can use your imagination.

Macy paid two native men a large sum of money and instructed them to creep into Warwick’s bedroom in the middle of the night and place an earwig on his pillow. He went to sleep that night with a smile on his face and dreamed about the horrible fate that was about to befall his friend.

The next morning, when Macy came down to breakfast, Warwick seemed bright and cheerful. He watched the old man closely, looking for any signs of discomfort.

Just then, Macy felt a strange tickling sensation in his own ear. When he poked his finger into his ear, he discovered that he was bleeding. Jumping up from the table with a look of horror on his face, he shrieked, “The damn thing is in my ear!”

It appeared that the men he paid had made a terrible mistake and during the night they had gone into the wrong room and placed the earwig in the wrong man’s ear.

That was the beginning of weeks of unimaginable pain and agony. There was nothing the doctor could do for him. He lay in his room, tied to the bed with his wrists lashed to the headboard to prevent him tearing his ears off.

Day and night, he writhed and screamed as the earwig crept and crawled and twisted through his head, slowly driving him insane. Occasionally, when the earwig was resting, Macy would get a break from his torment, but when it woke up, he would scream and scream and scream.

The pain was so unbearable that being flayed alive, burned at the stake, put on the rack or even hanged by the neck would have been an act of mercy. Every time the doctor came to see him, Macy begged him to put him out off his misery.

Then something very unexpected happened. Miraculously, the earwig crawled out his other ear. Macy had come close to the brink off death, but he had survived the torment.

When he was well enough to talk, the doctor came in to see him.

“I suppose they’re going to call the police and have me arrested now,” said Macy.

“No,” said the doctor. “They’re not calling the police.”

“Why not?” Macy demanded. “I suppose they’re trying to avoid a scandal.”

“No, they’re taking pity on you. They know about your condition…”

“What do you mean?”

“You see, the earwig was a female,” said the doctor, “and it laid eggs…”
"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/thinginthecabin" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="THE THING IN THE CABIN"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="










The Thing in the Cabin is a scary story about a creature in the woods that has the power to control men’s minds.

￼

The old man was weak and sick. His body wouldn’t last much longer.

I made the old man get up and walk to the window. He looked out and saw them standing there in the snow. There were four hunters gathered outside the cabin. I saw them too, through his eyes.

The hunters carried long guns and they were shivering with the cold. One of them walked up and banged on the door.

“Hello in there!” he shouted. “Hello! We’re lost and we need a place to stay for the night!”

I pulled the old man away from the window and made him bar the door.

“We have a little money we can give you!” the hunter shouted. “We just need a warm place to spend the night and a little food if you can spare it. We’re freezing to death out here!”

I made the old man throw another log on the fire.

“You don’t need to be scared of us,” the hunter said. “We’ll leave our guns outside. We don’t mean you any harm!”

I made the old man pick up his rifle and aim it through a slit in the cabin door. Then, I giggled as I made him pull the trigger. There was a loud bang and one of the hunters dropped in the snow. He didn’t know what hit him. The others were taken off guard. They dragged their friend’s body away and took cover behind the trees.

Gunshots exploded, ripping through the wooden door and breaking some of the windows. I released my hold on the old man’s brain and he collapsed in a heap on the floor. I flew up the chimney and soared above the cabin. The gunshots stopped and the hunters retreated. They would be back.

I flew high above the treetops and followed them. When they stopped, I drifted down and landed in the branches of a tall tree. The hunters were below me. They were setting up camp and building a fire.

There were three of them now. A fat one, a skinny one and a bearded one. The dead one lay nearby, staining the snow red with his blood. I had no use for him.

The bearded one chopped wood with his axe. He looked healthy and strong. The skinny one was struggling to light the fire, while the fat one just sat there and watched. I listened as the fat one spoke to the others. He told them that they would camp there for the night and in the morning, they would attack the cabin and kill the old man. I sat there in the branches of the tree and waited for night to come.

When it was dark, the men curled up around their blazing fire and tried to get some sleep. I waited until they were lying still and then I dropped down noiselessly into the snow. I crept towards the fat man who was wrapped up in his fur coat, snoring peacefully. Slowly, I reached out and took hold of the fat man’s mind.

I made him get up and walk over to where the dead man lay in the snow. I made him kneel down beside the corpse and take out his hunting knife. Then, I made him saw through the neck of his dead friend. When he was done, I made him smear his face with blood. Then I made him pick up the severed head and carry it back to the fire.

I released my hold on the fat man’s mind and that’s where I left him, standing in front of the fire, smeared with blood and holding the dead man’s severed head. When he looked down and saw the head, he screamed and woke the others. They scrambled to their feet and stared in horror at the severed head the fat man was clutching.

I watched it all from the safety of the trees. There were shouts and more screams as the skinny one and the bearded one grabbed their guns and blasted the fat man until he lay in a bloody heap on the snow.

Now there were only two.

They sat by the fire and waited. I watched and waited too. They were waiting for dawn to arrive. Then, they would attack the cabin and kill the old man. The bearded one threw more wood on the fire. He was too scared to sleep. The skinny one was weaker. He lay down and closed his eyes.

I took my chance, creeping up to the skinny one and reaching into his mind. I made him take out his hunting knife. I made him slowly get to his feet. The bearded one stared at us, wondering what was going on. I made the skinny one leap across the flames and attack the bearded one.

The kinny one was weak and the bearded one was too strong for him. I knew he would lose the fight. I released his mind and flew into the trees to watch from a safe distance. There was a fierce struggle, but in the end, the bearded one prevailed. He plunged the hunting knife into his friend’s chest and left the skinny one to bleed out on the snow.

Now there was only one.

I flew back to the cabin and slipped down the chimney. The old man lay on the floor where I left him. I took hold of his mind again and we searched through the cabin. There was not much in the place that I could use.

In a rusty metal box, I found a pair of garden shears. The handles were rusty, but the blades were still sharp. I made the old man pick them up. I made him look out the window and, through his eyes, I saw the bearded one coming across the snow, his gun at the ready.

“Come out old man!” the bearded one cried. “Come out or I’ll kill you!”

He fired his gun and a bullet ripped through the cabin door.

I made the old man shout, “OK! I’m coming out!”

I made him open the garden shears and place the blades at either side of his neck. Then, I made him throw open the door and walk out into the sunlight. When the bearded one saw him, he stopped in his tracks and raised his gun.

“What are you up to old man?” he demanded.

The old man didn’t say a word. I wouldn’t let him.

￼

The bearded man cautiously approached.

“Why did you have to start shooting at us?” he asked. “We didn’t mean you any harm. We just needed a place to stay.”

The old man resisted me and for a moment, I lost control. A thin wail escaped his lips. “Help me!” he begged.

I regained control of his mind and, summoning all the strength he had in his withered arms, I made him slam the handles of the shears together. The blades snapped together, slicing off his head. It fell to the ground with a thud, then his body crumpled and collapsed in a bloody heap. My grip on his mind was broken and I floated upwards.

The bearded one was so shocked and stunned that all he could do was stare in horror at the terrible sight. I took advantage of his momentary weakness, dropping onto his shoulders and reaching into his brain to take charge.

Now, he was mine.

After we dragged the bodies into the cabin, we feasted on the remains until I was satiated. I made the bearded man throw another log on the fire and we sat down in the rocking chair. Together, we rocked back and forth, enjoying the heat from the roaring flames.

The bearded man was strong and healthy. His body would last a long time.






"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/girlthedoll" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="GIRL AND THE DOLL"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="








The Girl and the Doll is a creepy story about a teenager who notices a strange little girl and a doll that has matching clothes.

￼

I want to tell you a story about a girl and a doll. I know what you’re thinking: You’ve heard this story before. A little girl wants a doll, someone buys it for her and then the doll goes mental and kills everyone! Well, you’re wrong. This is a different kind of story.

It happened back in 2009 when I was 16 years old. One day, as I was walking home from school, I noticed that a new family had moved into the house at the end of my street. They were a young married couple and they had a little daughter who looked like she was around 6 years old.

She wore a white dress, white socks and black shoes. Her hair was long and black and she was holding a doll in her arms. The doll had a white dress and long black hair as well. In fact, it looked almost exactly like a miniature version of the girl.

Every day, on my way home from school, I saw the little girl. She was always sitting there outside her house, cradling the doll in her arms and watching me as I passed by. There was something about the way she stared at me and the cold, dark look in her eyes that really unnerved me.

At night, I couldn’t sleep. I was plagued by very strange dreams and woke up in a cold sweat. I could only vaguely remember the dreams, but they all involved the girl with the doll. This went on night after night and the lack of sleep left me exhausted.

There was an old lady who lived next door and she was very inquisitive. She was one of these old women who knows everything about everyone. She was always eavesdropping and sticking her nose into other people’s business. One day, as I was walking to school, she grabbed me by the arm and, in hushed tones, she said she had something to tell me.

She wanted to talk about the family who moved into the house at the end of the street. “You don’t want to mess with them,” she told me. They’re not good people. I’ve heard that they’re always on the move and never stay anywhere for long. And that daughter of theirs… Did you know that she’s adopted? She’s not right in the head either. I’ve heard rumors that she’s the offspring of the devil and that doll she carries around is not a doll at all, but a demon made in her image…”

I just rolled my eyes and walked away, dismissing it as the idle gossip of a crazy old woman. But, oh how silly I was. How I wish I had listened to the warnings of that crazy old woman.

A few days later, there was a knock on our front door. When I answered it, a young woman was standing there. She was the mother of the little girl with the doll.

“Hello,” she said. “I’m your neighbor and I’d like to ask you for a favor.”

“Sure,” I replied. “What is it?”

“Something unexpectedly came up,” she said. “I have to go on an errand and my husband doesn’t get home from work until later. I’ll only be gone for a few hours, but I need someone to look after my daughter while I’m away. I know it’s short notice, but would you take care of her?”

“Of course,” I said. “What’s your daughter’s name?”

“Lisa,” the mother replied. “We need to leave now, so if you don’t mind…”

I followed the woman to her house and I waited while she rushed upstairs. When she returned, she was leading the little girl by the hand. As soon as I saw her, I was taken aback. There was something wrong with her.

Her eyes were completely black, like the eyes of a shark and she was still clutching that wretched doll in her arms. I don’t know what it was about the dool that creeped me out so much. Perhaps it was because it looked so much like the little girl that it was disturbing and uncanny.

Before I had a chance to back out, the mother said her goodbyes, then got into the car and drove away. Without a word, little Lisa reached up and took me by the hand. Her skin was ice-cold to the touch and it sent a shiver down my spine.

“Play with me,” she said.

We went upstairs to her bedroom, but as soon as I closed the door, I began to feel uneasy. I could detect a strange and unpleasant smell in the room, but I couldn’t figure out what it was or where it was coming from.

I played with Lisa for about 30 minutes, but then I began to feel a tightness in my chest. I broke out into a cold sweat and my stomach was churning. I felt like I was going to vomit.

“I have to go,” I gasped.

All of a sudden, Lisa scrambled to her feet and cried out, “No! You are going to stay with me forever! And we’ll play all the time!”

She stared at me with those cold, black eyes and I felt like I was going to faint. I was frightened and wanted to get out of the room, but when I tried to open the door, the handle wouldn’t turn. I began rattling it and pulling on it, but it was no use. I ran to the window amd tried to open it, but it wouldn’t budge. No matter what I tried, I couldn’t open it.

Then I remembered the warning of the old woman and cursed myself for not listening to her. I was trembling with fear, but I decided to recite a prayer.

“Our Father who art in heaven, hallowed be thy name…”

As soon as I uttered those words, the little girl let out an ear-splitting screech. She screamed so loud that I thought I would go deaf and I had to clasp my hands over my ears, but I never stopped reciting that prayer.

“Thy kingdom come, thy will be done, on earth as it is in heaven…”

The girl dropped the doll and it fell to the floor. All of a sudden, it came to life and came at me, gnashing its teeth and scratching with its clawed hands like a feral animal. I tried to kick it away, but it jumped at my neck and tried to tear my thoat out.

I fell backwards on the bed, desperately trying to fight the doll off. It was a terrible struggle. The doll was thrashing back and forth, scraping me and tearing at my clothes. Every time it got its hands around my neck, it started to throttle me.

Eventually, I got the upper hand. I grabbed it by the legs and swung it with all my might, smashing its head against the wall. It hit the wall so hard that it left a dent in the plaster. A crack split the doll’s face in two and thick black smoke began pouring out.

“Give us this day, our daily bread, and forgive us our trespasses as we forgive those who trespass against us…”

The doll lay on the floor, shaking and wriggling, flopping back and forth like a dying fish. The doll’s head split wider and the smoke billowing out of it grew thicker and thicker.

“And lead us not into temptation but deliver us from evil. Amen!”

When I finished reciting the prayer, Lisa was lying in the middle of the room, unconscious and the doll was little more than a steaming pile of molten plastic, hissing and bubbling on the carpet.

Just then, Lisa’s mother came home. She ran up the stairs and burst into the room, demanding to know what had happened. I tried to explain, but I couldn’t get the words out. I threw up all over the floor.

When Lisa regained consciousness, she said that she remembered nothing, nothing at all. I looked at her eyes. The blackness was gone and now they were a bright, vibrant shade of blue.

Three years later, when she was only 9 years old, Lisa died suddenly. She drank an entire bottle of bleach and it corroded her insides. She died in tremendous pain, screaming and crying in agony as her organs slowly broke down and dissolved. The doctors ruled it an accident, but everybody suspected she had taken her own life. Her parents were devastated. Nobody could explain why a girl so young would do such a thing.

A week after the funeral, her mother and father moved out of the house. It held too many bad memories. As they were going through Lisa’s bedroom and packing up her belongings, they found something glued to the back of her mirror. It was a photo of Lisa and the doll.

On the other side, written in a childish scrawl, was a message: “She has returned to us, for those who answer our call will be damned forever!”

"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/laughingman" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="LAUGHING MAN"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="



The Laughing Man is a scary story about two men who go into the jungles of Africa and try to trap a rare species of ape. It is based on an old horror comic that appeared in Creepy #95.

￼

There was a doctor who worked in a remote village in Africa. He was the only white person for miles and he had spent half his life taking care of the local villagers, providing them with medical care and medicine.

One day, a white man stumbled into the village. He could barely walk, but he was laughing like a maniac.

“Ha Ha Ha… Hee Hee Hee… Ha Ha Ha…”

His clothes were tattered and torn and his hands and knees were covered in blood. His eyes were wild and he looked exhausted. It seemed like he was out of his mind.

The doctor gave him some water and tended to his wounds, but the man couldn’t stop laughing…

“Ha Ha Ha… Hee Hee Hee… Ha Ha Ha…”

The doctor gave him a sedative and put him to bed, so he could get some rest.

￼

The man slept for hours and when he woke up, the doctor gave him some food and tried to find out how he had come to be there.

“What happened to you?” the doctor asked. “What are you doing all alone out here in the jungle?”

“I wasn’t alone,” the laughing man replied. “I came with my partner Jack Hunter. We were on an expedition to find the legendary Wahki… That’s what the locals call them… A rare species of ape… The Africans say they’re intelligent apes… almost as intelligent as a human… maybe even more intelligent… We wanted to capture one and bring it back to civilization to put it on display. It was supposed to make us very rich…”

“We tried to hire a guide to take us into the valley of the apes, but none of the locals dared to go there. They were afraid of the apes. We weren’t going to let that stop us, so be bought a canoe and headed down the river on our own.”

￼

“When we came to the valley of the apes, we made camp. Hunter unpacked the traps and set them up in a clearing in the jungle. We hid in the bushes and watched those traps for three whole days, but we caught nothing. The apes were too smart for us. They knew what we were up to. They weren’t going to fall for simple traps.”

“Hunter had a better idea. We dug a pit in the clearing. It was 10 feet deep and filled with sharp wooden spikes. Then, we covered it over with branches and leaves and went back to our camp to wait.”

“We didn’t have to wait very long. In the middle of the night, we heard a loud scream. A horrible, gurgling animal scream. We rushed out to check on the pit and found a dead ape, impaled on the sharp wooden spikes.”

￼

“We dragged the corpse out and laid it on the ground. We had what we came for… a dead ape… and I wanted to go home. Hunter had other ideas. He wanted to capture a live one.”

“I tried to talk him out of it, but there was no reasoning with him. Nothing I could say would dissuade him. He took out a knife and started skinning the ape’s body. As he worked, I nervously watched the jungle around us. It was dark, but I could feel the eyes of the other apes watching us. I couldn’t shake the creeping fear that they knew we had killed one of them and the rest would come to take revenge. When Hunter finished skinning the ape, he put on it’s skin and wore it like a costume.”

￼

“We removed the sharp wooden spikes from the pit and placed a big log across it. Disguised in his ape costume, Hunter balanced on the log and I covered the pit up with branches and leaves again. His plan was to trick one of the other apes into coming closer, so it would fall into the trap. He crouched there on the log and waited while I went back to our camp.”

￼

“It was almost dawn and I was just about to doze off, when I heard the scream. I rushed out to check the pit, but it was empty and my friend Hunter was nowhere to be seen. I called out his name, but there was no reply. I searched for hours, but I could find no trace of him. I was about to give up hope, when I spotted a figure in the jungle.”

“It was Hunter. He was crouched down under a tree, naked as the day he was born and he was just staring at me with a blank look on his face.”

￼

“Hunter!” I cried. “Good Lord! What happened to you? I thought you were dead. Why didn’t you answer me?”

“Hunter didn’t say a word. Slowly, he rose to his feet and he just stood there staring at me. And then… Ha Ha Ha… and then… Hee Hee Hee… and then… He took it off… Ha Ha Ha… Hee Hee Hee…”

The man was shaking and laughing so much, he could barely control himself. His body was wracked by spasms of madness.

“What do you mean?” the doctor asked. “What did he take off?”

Giggling like a maniac, the man struggled to finish his story.

“Ha Ha Ha… Hee Hee Hee… He took it off… Ha Ha Ha… The ape took off Hunter’s skin!”
"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/allyoucaneat" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="ALL YOU CAN EAT"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="







All You Can Eat is a scary story about a young boy and his father.

￼

When I was a child, my father always used to say, “If you kill something, you eat it.” I suppose that sounds reasonable enough, but my dad always took things a bit too far.

I remember the first time it happened. I was only 3 years old. I was stomping on ants. “Scrape them up and eat them, Son!” he growled. I wouldn’t do it. I cried and tried to run away, but he grabbed me and shoved the ants into my mouth, one by one. Afterwards, I threw up.

One day, when I was 4, my father caught me pulling the wings off flies. “You can eat them now or eat them later,” he said. I started crying, but he picked up a fly and made me open my mouth. Then, he dropped it in and forced me to swallow it. For weeks afterwards, I thought I could feel the fly buzzing around inside me.

When I was 6 years old, I made a bow and arrow out of a stick and a piece of string. I was running around the backyard, shooting arrows into the bushes when a bird flew by. I accidentally hit it and it fell to the ground at my feet. My father was watching at the window. “Bring it inside!” he yelled.

My dad made me watch as he plucked off all the feathers, cleaned the bird and gutted it. Then, he tossed it in a pot of boiling water. When it was cooked, he put it on a plate and set it down in front of me. It looked like a tiny little chicken. “Now eat it,” he ordered. Tears rolled down my cheeks. My father stood over me and made sure I ate the whole thing.

My dad wasn’t all that bad. He bought me a puppy for my 8th birthday. A few months later, he decided to teach me how to drive a car. As we were backing out of the driveway, I heard a crunch and hit the brakes. We got out of the car and when I saw my beloved pet dog, squashed under one of the rear wheels, I fell to my knees and burst into tears.

“You know the rules,” my dad said.

I started shaking my head and crying, “No! No! No! No!”

My dad picked up the dead dog, but I took off running into the fields. I spent the next two days and nights sleeping rough in the woods. I was cold and hungry, but I didn’t want to go home.

On the third night, I waited until it was late and all the lights were out. Then, I climbed in the kitchen window as quietly as possible and looked in the fridge.

All of a sudden, I heard my father’s voice coming from the darkness. “Your dinner’s on the table,” he said.

He flicked on the lights and nodded to a big platter on the table. There lay my pet dog, roasted to a crisp, with an apple in its jaws.

I tried to run, but he grabbed me by the scruff of the neck and pushed me down on a chair. I couldn’t stop screaming and crying, but he didn’t care.

Picking up a knife and fork, my father carved pieces off the dog and put them on my plate. He made me eat until I felt my stomach was about to burst.

Something inside me snapped that night. I couldn’t take it anymore. Then and there, I began plotting to run away.

Early one morning, just before dawn, I got dressed and packed a bag. Then, I quietly opened my bedroom door and tip-toed into the hallway.

Standing at the top of the stairs was my father. He had been waiting for me.

“Going somewhere?” he chuckled.

I tried to run past him, but he stepped in my way. I accidentally slammed into him and he lost his balance. Everything seemed to happen in slow motion. I watched my father fall backwards and I reached out to grab him, but I missed.

He tumbled down the stairs, hitting every step on the way down and landed at the bottom with a dull thud. I ran down the stairs to try and help him, but it was useless. His neck was twisted at an odd angle and his dead eyes stared up at me. I started crying uncontrollably.

I was still crying as I switched on the oven and went out to the shed to fetch the axe.


"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/oldman" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="THE OLD MAN"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="









The Old Man is a scary story about a mysterious character who lives in an old, crumbling house by the sea. It is based on an old horror tale by H.P. Lovecraft called “The Terrible Old Man”.

￼

The old man lived all alone in an ancient, crumbling house near the sea. His garden was overgrown and neglected and his house was surrounded by old, gnarled trees.

He was a recluse and rarely ventured out of his home. No one knew his name or where he came from. Those who saw him said he had long black hair, a wrinkled, leathery face and dark, piercing eyes. Sometimes, neighbors would see him hobbling around on a cane.

The old man was rumored to be both extremely rich and extremely feeble. There were rumors that he kept a fortune in gold hidden away somewhere in his dusty abode.

Young boys loved to taunt the old man, shouting at him and calling him names whenever they passed his house. Sometimes they would even throw rocks at his house and break the window panes of his dwelling. Occasionally, some of the older kids would steal up to the house and peer in through the dusty windows just to catch a glimpse of him.

One night, three criminals decided to rob the old man. They parked their car outside his house and sat there in the darkness, waiting until the time was right. Their plan was to threaten the old man and make him tell them where his fortune was hidden. If that didn’t work, then they would beat it out of him.

The moon was shining down on the ancient house and the wind was blowing through the branches of the old, gnarled trees. When the lights in the house went off, two of the criminals got out of the car and made their way up to the front door. They put on black masks to cover their faces and rang the doorbell.

The third criminal sat in the car, waiting nervously for his companions to return. He kept checking his watch and wondering what was taking them so long. Just after midnight, he heard hideous screams coming from inside the ancient house.

He hoped they didn’t beat the old man to death. If he died before he could reveal where his treasure was hidden, they would have to search the whole house from top to bottom. That could take all night.

Just then, he heard footsteps coming down the path and the sound of someone opening the lock on the gate. In the dim glow of the street-lights, he strained his eyes to see, but when he looked, he didn’t see what he had expected.

The next morning, an abandoned car was found parked outside the old man’s house. The police checked the licence plates and discovered that it had been stolen. They returned it to its rightful owner.

A few days later, three unidentified bodies washed up on the beach. The corpses were horribly mangled and mutilated. Every single bone in their bodies had been broken and their heads were crushed beyond recognition. The three bodies had been reduced to little more than three rubbery piles of flesh.

The discovery of the bodies on the beach caused a lot of excitement in the little seaside town. That summer, it was all anyone could talk about and nobody could figure out who they were or what had happened to them. Still, whenever people passed by the old man’s house, they felt a little involuntary shiver of fear run down their spines. Young boys didn’t shout at the old man or call him names anymore and nobody dared to sneak up to his house and peer in his windows for fear of what they might see.





"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/humanchair" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="HUMAN CHAIR"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="






The Human Chair is a scary story about a strange person who carries out a very disturbing plan. It is based on an old Japanese story by Edogawa Rampo.

￼

Hello. What you are about to read will shock you. I need to confess the strange and terrible crime I have committed and I can’t bear to keep my secret any longer. I beg you not to stop reading.

For years, I have hidden myself away from the world. You see, I am hideously ugly… Too ugly to describe. You would be shocked and horrified at the sight of my face. I was a miserable and wretched creature, because I never knew love. I never felt the affectionate touch of a hand or the warm feeling of a pair of lips brushing against mine.

I was a carpenter by trade and I worked all day in a factory, making furniture. My specialty is making chairs. My skilled hands carved the wood, screwed the pieces together, fashioned the back-rests and arm-rests and did the upholstry, padding the cushions and sewing the covers. As I worked, I felt like an artist creating a great masterpiece.

When my chairs were finished, I would always test them out to make sure they were comfortable. It gave me a great thrill to imagine all the different people who would sit on the chair I created. Unlike me, they had wonderful, happy lives. They had someone they loved and who would love them back. Every time I thought of them, I felt nothing but misery and despair.

One day, I was designing a new type of chair and, as I worked, a very strange idea began to take form in my mind. I changed the design and made a hollow space inside. It was a cavity large enough to fit a human body. Of course, I had to take out a lot of the wooden framework and the springs inside.

The knees would be just below the seat, the head and upper body would be inside the back-rest. Someone could sit inside the chair and no one would ever know they were there. I left a small space for supplies, like food and drinks and I even included a little potty for pee and poo. By the time I was finished, the chair had become a miniature home.

I stripped off my clothes and climbed inside the chair. Can you imagine how strange that felt? It was a tight fit, but I managed to get used to it after a while. I was in complete darkness, but I could hear what was going on around me. I heard my colleagues walking around the factory, looking for me. They had no idea that I was right under their noses.

After a while, some delivery men loaded me into a truck and transported me to a furniture store. They put me on display in the middle of the shop floor and left me there. I was perfectly concealed and nobody was any the wiser. I was like a crab or a turtle, but instead of a shell, I had my chair.

Almost as soon as I arrived, customers started testing out the chair. I can’t tell you how many unknown bottoms sat down on me. Some of them had big, fat bottoms like a jellyfish and others had thin, bony bottoms like a skeleton. Some had firm buttocks like a horse and others had chubby buttocks, bouncing up and down on me like a rubber ball.

It was an amazing feeling. I could feel the warmth of their flesh through the material. Their shoulders rested against my chest and their arms and hands rested on mine. Not one of them suspected that the soft cushion they were sitting on was actually little old me.

Previously, because of my grotesque and disturbing appearance, people had always recoiled at the sight of me, but now my skin was virtually touching theirs through a thin layer of cloth. Hidden inside the chair, I imagined myself hugging them, kissing them and wrapping my arms around them in a passionate embrace.

Of course, it was a strange sort of existence. After spending so long inside the chair, sitting in the same position, my muscles started to wither away. I could barely move and my body was crooked and bent. I was folded up like a contortionist, but I didn’t care. All I could think about was the exquisite feeling of having people sit on me.

One day, somebody bought my chair. The delivery men picked me up, put me in the back of a van and brought me to the home of a nice family. They put me in their living room, facing the TV. Within days, every member of the family had sat on me at least once. I was in heaven.

But there was one member of the family I loved more than all of the others. This person was very special to me and, as time went on, I began to fall in love with them. I couldn’t help myself.

Whenever they sat down on me, I tried to make my knees as comfortable as possible for them. Whenever they leaned back on me, I would embrace them more warmly and make them nice and snug. When they felt tired, I would move my knees back and forth, gently rocking them to sleep.

You may think I was mad, but I was madly in love with this person. I became obsessed with them and I longed for them to return my feelings. I reached the point where I felt that if only they knew I was there, they would fall in love with me too.

The person loved to read, so I came up with a cunning plan. I wrote sown my story and submitted it to a website they frequented.

By now, you’ve probably guessed who I am talking about.

That’s right… It is you.

I have been in your home for so long, you’ve probably forgotten where I came from. Every night, I crawl out of the chair and sneak upstairs to watch you sleep. I can’t bear to be away from you for a moment. I love you and I think you could love me too… if only you saw me.

Now, after you finish reading this, please turn around and look at me. I’ll be waiting. Don’t be afraid. Come and sit down on my knees. I miss your touch.





"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/cleankill" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="CLEAN KILL"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="



Clean Kill is a scary horror story about a young woman who encounters a strange man in the woods. It was inspired by a an old horror comic called Tales of Terror.

￼

It was a cold and windy night. Karen Ledger was standing on the dock, clutching her suitcase and waiting anxiously for a boat to arrive. It was dark and she glanced around nervously. She had the strangest feeling that someone was watching her.

All of a sudden, she heard a rustling noise in the bushes behind her. When she whirled around, she was shocked to see a man standing there. He was dressed in ragged clothing and he was clutching an axe in his hands.

“Who… Who are you?” she cried.

“That don’t matter,” the man replied with a smile. “You look good… Real good… I bet you taste good too…”

Karen let out a horrified scream as the man raised the axe above his head. He brought it crashing down with a loud Thunk! The razor-sharp blade embedded itself in her skull, killing her instantly.

The man was pleased. It was a clean kill. Quickly, he grabbed her by the legs and dragged her body into the bushes. He carried her through the trees and back to his cabin, set back in a remote part of the forest.

He dumped her in the bathtub, pulled off her clothes, then went out to the shed to fetch his chainsaw. It was messy work, but after a few minutes, he had chopped her body into pieces.

The man roasted the legs in the oven and made a soup from eyeballs and severed fingers. Then, he sat at the table and gobbled down as much as he could eat, savoring the taste of human flesh.

Later that night, while he was going through her coat pockets, he found a letter. As soon as he read it, his eyes grew wide and his face went pale.

“Dear Ms. Ledger,

Your test results came back. We regret to inform you that you have Leprosy and it is contagious. We have arranged for you to be treated at a special isolation clinic. It is located on a remote island off the coast. A boat will meet you at the dock on Friday night at 11PM. Please make sure you are there…"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/lookatme" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="LOOK AT ME"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="


Look at Me is a scary true story about a teenage boy who has a creepy encounter one stormy night when his parents go out and leave him home alone. It is a real experience from a user named theaterguy.

￼

One evening, when I was in my junior year of high school, my mom and dad went out, leaving me home alone. I had a lot of homework to do, so I spent the whole evening sitting at the desk in my bedroom.

My parents left the house around 6 PM. While I was doing my homework, I put on my headphones and listened to loud music. There was a big storm that night and my desk was facing the window, so I could see the rain and the lightning outside.

My parents got back around 11 PM. When I saw their car drive up, I took off the headphones. As soon as my mom opened the front door and came inside, I heard heard her shout my name.

“What on earth happened in here!?” she demanded in an angry voice.

Confused, I ran downstairs. My mom was standing in the hallway with a furious look on her face. She pointed at the floor and yelled, “Was this you!?”

I looked down and saw that the carpet was covered in muddy footprints.

“I have no idea how those got there,” I said. “I spent the whole night at my desk, doing my homework.”

I watched as the look on her face changed from anger to confusion, and then to fear. We both realized it at the same time. Someone else must have been in the house.

We followed the trail of footprints, trying to make sense of the whole situation. They started at the back door, which we usually left unlocked. Then we noticed something else. The footprints started at the backdoor, but there was no trail of footprints leaving through the back door.

All of a sudden, we hear something a loud, pounding noise that echoed throughout house. Then, the sound of the front door being wrenched open and slammed shut again. WHAM!

We all ran into the garage and locked the door behind us. My mom took out her cell phone and called the police.

“Please come quickly!” she shouted. “Someone’s in our house!”

After what seemed like hours, a patrol car arrived with two police officers, a male and a female. One officer stayed with us in the garage while his partner went through the house, searching it room by room. When she came back, the female officer told us that there was no one in the house and it was safe to go back in.

As we were all breathing a sigh of relief, she asked, “Whose bedroom is upstairs on the left?”

My parents looked at me.

“It’s mine,” I told the officer.

She asked us to follow her. As we walked through the house, we could see the trail of muddy footprints leading from the back door, through the living room, through the hallway, up the stairs, into my parents’ bedroom and then towards my room. They stopped at my doorway.

The female officer pointed at my door, which had been open the whole night. Scrawled on it, in black marker, was the following:

8:47 I see you

8:53 You forgot to lock the back door

8:59 You seem focused

9:24 Turn around

9:47 Look at me

10:15 Look at me

10:37 Look at me

10:49 Look at me

For more than two hours, someone had been standing in my doorway, watching me. To this day, I still shudder to think what would have happened if I had turned around…

"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/shush" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="SHUSH"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="






Shush is a true scary story about a girl who is tormented by terrible nightmares whenever she stays in her grandmother’s cottage. It is supposed to be a true story, told by a girl named Sabina.

￼

My name is Sabina. When I was a little girl, my parents took me to visit my grandmother. She lived in a little village in the countryside. Her cottage was very small and there was only one bedroom. My grandmother slept in one bed, my parents slept in the other and I had to sleep on some cushions on the floor.

We stayed there for a few weeks and I was troubled by terrible nightmares. Every night, I would wake up screaming. My parents tried to calm me down and asked me what was wrong. All I could tell them was that a man was coming to get me.

I can still remember the cause of my terror. Every night, I saw a shadowy figure emerge from behind the curtains in the corner of the room. He was pitch black and all I could make out was his outline. He was tall and hairy.

I would watch in horror as he came crawling towards me, with a sickening slowness. He came up to me and whispered something in my ear and just as I was about to scream, he would placed a finger against his lips and whisper, “Shush… shush… shush…”

He tortured me every night to the point where I dreaded going to sleep. As time went on, he began to appear not only at night, but also during the day.

One evening, we were all watching TV in the living room and at some point I happened to glance to my left. The curtains slowly drew back and I saw the man standing there, staring silently at me. He raised his hand, put his finger to his lips and whispered, “Shush… shush… shush…”

I let out a horrified scream and immediately told my mother what I had seen. She got up and went over to the curtains, pulling them back and forth and showing me that there was nothing there, but of course by then he had already disappeared.

When the holiday was over, we went back to our apartment in the city and the nightmares stopped. After that, my grandmother would always come to visit us instead, so we never went to her cottage on vacataion again. As time went on, I stopped thinking about the man and eventually forgot about him altogether.

One Summer, when I was 13 years old and my little brother was 5 years old, we went to stay with my grandmother again. My parents were in the kitchen, having a cup of tea with my grandmother. THey asked me to get my little brother ready for bed. While I was preparing a mattress on the floor for both of us to sleep on, my little brother was sitting on one of the beds.

I noticed that he was being unusually quiet. When I looked up, I saw that he was staring at something.

“What’s wrong?” I asked him.

Then, suddenly, he jerked head around and looked at me, his eyes wide with fear.

“Sabina,” he said, pointing at the curtains. “The Shush man is standing there…”

Needless to say, my brother and I spent the night sleeping in the kitchen and we never went to visit my grandmother’s cottage again."
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/otherme" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="OTHER ME"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"

            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="








The Other Me is a true scary story about a young couple who are living together and begin to experience some strange incidents in their apartment. It is supposedly a true story that happened in Russia.

￼

A month ago, my girlfriend and I got engaged. We moved into a new apartment and began living together. It was the first time either of us had shared an apartment, so it was a new experience for both of us. We were deeply in love. I knew she was the one I wanted to spend the rest of my life with and I thought she felt the same about me.

Everything went well until two weeks ago, when I noticed that my girlfriend was acting very strangely. She became so attached to me that it felt like she couldn’t stand being away from me for a moment.

One evening, she said to me, “Darling, when you’re not at home, I still feel you near me.”

I didn’t attach much importance to these words. I thought she was just being affectionate. However, a few days later, she told me something else.

“Whenever you’re at work,” she said, “I often hear your voice… As if you are calling my name.”

This began to happen more and more as the days went by and I started to get a little worried about her. One day, when I arrived home from work, I found her sitting silently at the kitchen table, staring blankly at the wall with a glazed look in her eyes. I grabbed a chair, sat down beside her and asked her what was the matter.

“I think there’s something wrong with me,” she murmured.

“Why do you think that?” I asked.

“I saw you today,” she said. “You walked from the kitchen into the bedroom and then you stood back to me, staring out the window.”

“But I was at work all day,” I said.

“I know,” she replied with a sigh.

That’s when I really began to worry. I suspected that my girlfriend was losing her mind and starting to have hallucinations.

Over the next few days, she kept telling me that she saw me in the apartment when I was at work. She could even describe exactly what I was wearing. My girlfriend was also acting more and more strange. She was getting more and more quiet and she was terrified of being left alone. Sometimes, she would just sit there, silently staring at me.

Last night, my girlfriend was very tired and decided to go to bed early. I held her hand and sat on the edge of the bed as she was falling asleep.

Just before she nodded off, she said, “You’re not here.”

“Honey, I’m right here,” I replied. “Don’t worry. Everything is fine.”

“No, you’re not here,” she said. “You’re in the kitchen.”

Just then, I heard a dull noise coming from the kitchen. It sounded like a chair scraping across the linoleum. Then, I heard the sound of footsteps walking down the hallway. Fear gripped my heart. I didn’t know what to do.

All of a sudden, the handle on the bedroom door began to turn and the door slowly began to open. Maybe it’s just a draft, I thought as my eyes grew wide with fear. But it wasn’t a draft. The door swung open and I saw a man standing there in the doorway.

It was me.

It’s difficult to describe exactly what I saw. It was me… but at the same time, it wasn’t me. It was as if I was staring at myself in a mirror, but the other me had cold, lifeless eyes.

The other me looked at me for a moment, then turned and left, shutting the door behind him. It took me a moment to recover from the shock and then I sprang off the bed and ran after him.

The hallway was empty. I checked the kitchen, then the bathroom, but he was nowhere to be found. The other me simply vanished. It was terrifying.

And then, as I stood in the hallway, trying to figure out what had just happened, trying to calm myself down and convince myself that it was just a hallucination, I heard a faint voice coming from the kitchen.

It wasn’t my voice, it was the voice of my girlfriend.

“We are here to stay,” she said. “Forever.”

I realized that my girlfriend wasn’t in the kitchen. She was lying in the bedroom, exactly where I had left her just seconds before. I was so frightened, I started trembling like a leaf.

I ran into the bedroom, grabbed my girlfriend and dragged her with me, out the front door. We left the apartment that very moment and spent the night in my parents’ house.

Tomorrow, we will go back to pick up our things. I still can’t understand what happened in that apartment, but neither of us can bear to spend another night there. Hopefully, when we pick up our things, all will be well and no one will be there.





"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/lakevermilion" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="LAKE VERMILION"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="





Lake Vermilion is a true scary story about a group of friends who see something horrifying when they are camping in a cabin one night. It is based on a supposedly true story that actually happened to a user named MHop99.

￼

The story you are about to read is TRUE and not made up in any way. One of my friends actually suffered a nervous breakdown after the incident and needed to go into counseling.

I had three really good friends and their names were Kevin, Ryan and Tommy. Every Summer, our parents would take us on vacation. We always stayed in a remote cabin in the forests of Minnesota. The cabin was located on a large island in the middle of Lake Vermilion.

Eventually, when we were old enough, our parents let us go to the cabin on our own for the first time. When we got there, we parked the car on a gravel road beside the lake. Then, we had to take a boat across the lake about a half mile to reach the cabin. There were a few other cabins on the island, but they were all at least half mile away.

The cabin was quite small and it only had a kitchen, a bathroom and 2 bedrooms. At night, it was pitch black. There were no street lights for miles and the only light came from the moon. There were no curtains on the windows, so when you were sleeping there at night, you could see the moon shining down on the trees and the lake outside.

On the third night of our trip, we set up a campfire by the edge of the lake. The moon was full and the pale white glow was shimmering across the lake. We were gazing up at the stars when all of a sudden we heard a splashing sound, as if something was moving about on the water.

Ryan suddenly stood up and pointed, saying “What the hell is that?”

We all looked in the direction he was pointing, peering into the darkness. After a while, I could make out what he was pointing at. I’ll never forget the feeling of terror that came over me. The hair on the back of my neck stood up and goosebumps appeared on my arms. I was paralyzed with fear.

Out in the middle of the lake, there was a woman’s head. It was just floating there on the surface of the water, staring directly at us. She had pale white skin and long black hair that was matted across her face. The rest of her was submerged or not even there.

We tried to tell ourselves it was just a loon. They’re black and white birds that hunt at night, diving deep into the water. It didn’t look like a loon, but that’s what we tried to convince ourselves it was. We threw some more wood on the fire and tried to forget about it, but it still gave me the creeps.

About an hour later, I had to go to the toilet, so I walked down to the edge of the dock and peed into the lake. Looking out over the moonlit lake, I noticed the thing was still there, but now it was much closer. It still looked like a woman’s head and it still seemed to be staring right at me. Its face was still extremely pale, as if it hadn’t been out in the sun for years and I could easily make out some facial features… the eyes and the nose.

A feeling of incredible unease came over me as I realized it couldn’t be a loon. There was no way a loon could tread water for that length of time. There were no ripples around it either. It wasn’t moving at all. It was just standing there, stiff as a board, submerged in the water.

I immediately zipped up my pants and ran back up the dock to where my friends were, sitting around the campfire. I told them what I had seen, but none of them dared to go down the dock to take a closer look. We tried to tell ourselves it was just a log or a tree branch, jutting out of the water. I could tell everyone else felt uneasy too. None of us really believed that.

We went back into the cabin and shut the door, locking it behind us. It was very late and we needed to sleep. None of us mentioned the thing in the lake. We were all trying to avoid talking about it.

There were no curtains on the windows and as I was getting ready for bed, I couldn’t help taking one last look. Peering out the window, I could see the lake clearly, illuminated by the full moon, but the thing wasn’t there anymore. It had completely vanished. I let out a sigh of relief, thinking the log must have floated away or else it just sank below the surface. Or perhaps it had been a loon after all and it had finally flown away.

It was very hot that night and we had to sleep with the windows open. My friend Tommy and I slept in one bedroom and my two other friends, Kevin and Ryan, slept in the other bedroom. We left our bedroom doors open.

I was finding it hard to sleep. It was the middle of Summer and there wasn’t even a slight breeze. The heat was stifling. As I lay there, I thought I could hear someone walking around outside the cabin. I kept my eyes tightly shut and tried to tell myself it was just my imagination. It sounded like someone with bare, wet feet, pacing back and forth. I was trembling with fear, but I felt so weak, I couldnt move.

The footsteps sounded like they were walking up the steps to the cabin door. I wanted to shout out to my friends, but I was frozen in terror. Then, the footsteps turned around and sounded like they were running down the steps and towards the lake.

After a while, the footsteps faded away and there was only silence. I reached over and shook my friend Tommy. He was already awake and he claimed he had heard the footsteps as well. Just then, I was startled to see Ryan come running into the room. When he stepped into the moonlight, I could see his face and the expression on it was very disturbing.

“We need to leave,” he croaked.

“Why?” I asked. “What did you hear?”

“Let’s just go!” he insisted. “Let’s get to the boat! It’s time to go!”

He wouldn’t answer. He just ran back into his room. We followed him and found Kevin sitting on his bed, already packing up his things. Ryan was running around, frantically grabbing his stuff and stuffing it into a bag.

“What’s wrong!?” I demanded. “Ryan, what the hell is wrong with you?! Tell us!”

He just stopped in his tracks and stared at me. There was a haunted look in his eyes. I will never forget what he said.

He told us he was turning over in his bed to get more comfortable when he suddenly saw at the top right corner of his window. Someone was peeking in. As soon as he set eyes on it, the face vanished. He said all he saw was long black hair, hanging down the window, ghostly-white skin and one large eye staring at him.

When he said that, it chilled us to the bone. We realized that if the face was in the top right corner of the window, that meant the thing had to be damn near 8 feet tall… or else floating in mid-air. I felt like I was going to be sick.

“Let’s just go!” Ryan said in a very serious tone. “Let’s just go NOW!”

We all agreed and packed our stuff as quickly as we could. We grabbed our bags and ran out of the cabin, oausing only to lock the door behind us. As we scrambled down the front steps, I glanced to the side and saw footprints… bare, wet fooprints… in the dirt all around the cabin.

We ran down to the boat and threw our stuff in. We untied the boat from the dock and sped off. I looked back over my shoulder and stared at the island, but I didn’t see anything moving. However, I had the strangest feeling that someone or something was watching us.

When we finally reached the other side of the lake, we tied up the boat, stuffed our backpacks in the car and drove off. We had been driving for about 10 minutes when, out of the blue, Ryan suddenly broke down sobbing.

He kept saying over and over, “What was it guys? Oh God! What did I see?”

On the way, we called our parents to tell them what had happened. Ryan was freaking out and we didn’t know what to do. They told us to just get home safely and quickly. My friend’s dad went up to the cabin a few days later and said he saw nothing out of the ordinary. However, he did mention that there were bare, wet footprints all around the cabin which he thought was odd.

Whatever Ryan saw in the window really hit him hard. After his breakdown, he had trouble sleeping and ended up having to go into therapy. They gave him some pills to calm him down and allow him to get a decent night’s sleep. As time went on, he recovered and ended up being fine, but to this day, he still can’t sleep unless the curtains on his window are completely shut.

To this day, I still cannot explain what we saw in the lake that night. I never went back to the cabin. Tommy and Kevin have both gone back and everything was fine, but Ryan refuses to go back and, frankly, I’m with him.










"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/doorhandle" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="THE DOOR HANDLE"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="




The Door Handle is a true scary story about a young man who decides to hitchhike home from college. It is based on an experience from a user named thatsapaddlin.

In the late 1970s, my uncle was studying medicine at the University of Chicago. One day, after class, he decided to hitchhike home. A man drove up and offered my Uncle a ride. He looked normal and seemed friendly, so my Uncle got in the car.

However, on the way, the man suddenly took a different route. My uncle told the man he was going the wrong way. The man looked at my Uncle, put his hand on his leg and smiled darkly at him.

“No son,” he said, “you’re coming with me”.

My Uncle froze and began to panic. When the car slowed down in traffic, he quickly opened the passenger door, jumped out and ran away without looking back.

A few years later, my uncle was watching TV when he saw something that made his blood run cold. There was a picture of the man that had picked him up. He had been arrested for the murder of at least 33 boys and young men.

￼

The man on the television was John Wayne Gacy. He was a notorious serial killer. The police found 26 bodies buried under his house. The creepiest thing of all was that he had removed the door handle from the passenger side door of his car to prevent his victims from escaping.
"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/boneless" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="THE BONELESS"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="







The Boneless is a scary true story about a shapeless white apparition that plagued the Shetland Islands many years ago. It was what they called a “Frittening” – a shapeless ghostly apparition that could cause people to die of sheer fright. It is based on an account found in the book “Shetland Traditional Lore” by Jessie Saxby.

￼

The Shetland Islands are a group of small islands off the coast of Scotland. Many years ago, the people of the Shetland Islands were plagued by a very unusual creature. They called it “The Boneless”.

Nobody who saw it could describe it properly. This was because no two people who encountered it ever saw the same thing. It always appeared at night when the veils between this world and the other are at their weakest.

One person said it looked like a large lump of white slop, another said it looked like a huge jellyfish, another claimed it was like a slimy white cloud. A thrid said it looked like a bag of wet wool and a fourth said it looked like an armless, legless, headless human torso.

Sometimes people would just catch a glimpse of some ghastly wet vile thing pressed up against a window, but in the blink of an eye, it would be gone and they could never be sure of what they had seen.

Even though it didn’t have legs, they said it could move faster than a dog and it could fly higher than a hawk, but it never made a sound. Those who were unlucky enough to set eyes on it were frightened out of their wits and found cowering in terror.

One night, a man was sitting in his house, reading the Bible by the light of a candle. All of a sudden, he heard a sickening splat, like the sound of a huge mass of wet meat slapping against the front door.

With his Bible clutched in one hand, he pulled open the door and looked out. By the light of the moon, he could see a puddle of slime on the front porch. His eyes followed the trail of slime and it led down the steps and into the darkness.

Just then, he noticed something moving in the dark. It was pale, white and shapeless, but he couldn’t make out what it was. He snatched an axe from the woodpile and followed the mysterious apparition.

With his bible in one hand and his axe in the other, he followed it down a road that led towards the cliffs, overlooking the sea. He caught up with it just as it was about to slide over the cliff and escape into the sea. The man hurled his axe at the thing and it stuck fast in the slimy creature.

He ran back to the house, where he gathered his servants and persuaded them to accompany him to the spot. The boneless thing was still there, silent and motionless, with the axe still sticking in it. None of them could tell whether it was alive or not. None of them could even tell what it looked like, because they all saw something different.

The men were frightened, so they hastily began to bury the thing, flinging earth over it until it was covered. Then, they dug a wide trench around it, so that nothing could get near it.

The next day, however, the man’s son heard his father telling people about the mysterious boneless thing and he became curious. The boy wanted to get a look at it himself.

When nobody was around, he went down to the heap of earth near the cliffs and jumped over the trench. He began digging into the earth with his hands. When he scooped out a handful of clay, he suddenly saw a strange, unearthly light and a white mist formed around him, like a dense fog.

The frightened boy scrambled to get away, but something rose out of the hole and began to slither toward him. It was pale, white and shapeless. He turned to run back to the house, but the thing overtook him. It slid up all over him and wrapped itself around him like a wet, heavy blanket.

He felt like he was being smothered. It was as cold as the night sea and it smelled like rotting flesh. Then, it tightened around him and he had the sickening feeling that he might be torn in two if it didn’t let go.

The horrible thing began dragging him toward the edge of the cliff. He could hear the waves crashing below. He tried to call out for help, but he was so scared that the scream died in his throat. He felt around with his one free hand and managed to grab onto a rock and hung on for dear life.

The boy was frightened out of his wits and all he could think to do was pray.

“Now I lay me down to sleep,” he muttered, “I pray the Lord my soul to keep; If I should die before I wake, I pray the Lord my soul to take…”

No sooner had he said that then the thing let go of him. It rolled over the cliff and disappeared. The boy lay there for a long time, clinging to the rock, shivering and shaking. Eventually, he managed to drag himself back to the house where he told his parents what had happened.

"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/onenight" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="ONE NIGHT"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"

            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="






One Night is a collection of scary true stories about real people having encounters with the paranormal, the unexplained or the downright weird. Whatever it was, it happened one night…

￼

\n1. The Attic Man

One night, I was house-sitting for my grandmother while she was away. I was suddenly awoken by her dog barking and snarling. When I got out of bed, I felt a cold breeze blowing through the house. I went to investigate and to my horror, I found that the attic stairs had been pulled down and there was a trail of muddy footprints leading down the stairs to the back door, which was wide open…

\n2. The Following Man

One night, a girl was walking home when she got the strangest feeling she was being watched. When she looked behind her, there was a man following her. She went into a hotel lobby to try and shake him off. She told the staff what was going on and they insisted on calling the police. When they arrived, the police found the man and brought him down to the station for questioning. After taking his fingerprints and a sample of his DNA, they got a match. It turned out he had murdered 3 women in the previous 3 weeks.

\n3. The Whispering Man

One night, I was lying in bed with my wife. Just as I was drifting off to sleep, I heard a strange whispering sound. It made the hair on the back of my neck stand on end. I opened my eyes and looked around, but there was nothing there. The next morning, my wife told me she had a very creepy dream. “I dreamed that we were in bed and I felt a strange presence in the room. When I looked around, I saw a man crouching at the foot of the bed. Then, he crawled up onto the bed and began whispering in your ear…”

\n4. The Gliding Man

One night, my friend and I were driving around the neighborhood. It was late and the streets were deserted. All of a sudden, we noticed someone walking along the sidewalk ahead of us. The person was wearing a black jacket with a hood. There was nothing unusual about that, but When we looked down, we realized that the figure didn’t have any legs. It didn’t seem to touch the ground at all and was just gliding along. The figure suddenly turned its head and looked right at us. We both screamed and I floored the accelerator and sped out of there. We only got a brief look at its face, but we both saw the same thing. Under the hood, there was nothing but a black, empty void. It didn’t have a face.

\n5. The Lightning Man

One night, I was lying in bed and it was raining outside. There was thunder and lightning and I couldn’t sleep. Our house was out in the middle of nowhere. There were no curtains on my bedroom window, so I had a view of the fields behind the house. It was pitch black outside, but every time the lightning struck, it illuminated the whole landscape for a split second. All of a sudden, during one flash, I caught a brief glimpse of a figure standing in the field. It was a man and he was completely black, except for his eyes which were glowing white. He was just standing out there, staring at the house. With every flash of lightning, he got closer and closer until he was right outside my window, staring in at me with those glowing eyes. Then, with the next flash of lightning, he was gone.

\n6. The Telephone Pole Man

One night, when I was just a kid, I was playing with my brother and sister in the living room. My little brother suddenly stopped, looked out the window and asked “Who’s that man?” We all went to the window to see what he was talking about. To our surprise, there was a pale white figure sitting on top of the telephone pole outside. It looked like a man and he was staring at us with a huge creepy smile. Then, he simply stood up, jumped off the pole and vanished before he hit the ground. It scared us so much that my sister won’t even talk about it now.

\n7. The Woods Man

One night, when I was 10 years old, I was bored and decided to explore the woods at the back of my house. It was dark and I wasn’t looking where I was going. I suddenly tripped and fell on the ground. When I got, I looked around, but I couldn’t see what I tripped over. I turned to go home and just then, from behind me, I heard a voice whisper “Don’t Leave”. It chilled me to the bone and I started running. I ran as fast as I could and I didn’t stop until I got home. When I looked back into the woods, I could see the dark silhouette of a man standing at the very edge of the woods. He was just standing there, watching me. It wasn’t a person. It was just a dark figure with no face and no eyes.

\n8. The Man in the Floor

One night, my aunt was sitting on the toilet. There was a small hole in the floor that had been there ever since we moved in. She just happened to look down at the hole and what she saw nearly scared the life out of her. There was a man standing in the basement looking right back up at her and he had a creepy smile on his face. My aunt screamed and came running out of the bathroom. My uncle and my dad went down the stairs, into the basement and looked around. They didn’t find anybody and there was no other way in or out of the basement. However, in the dust on the floor, they found footprints as if someone had been standing directly under the hole."
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/manwithredeyes" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="THE MAN WITH RED EYES"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="










The Man With Red Eyes is a true scary story about a little boy who has what he thinks is an imaginary friend.

￼

When I was just a little boy, I had an imaginary friend. At least, I thought he was an imaginary friend. Today, I’m not so sure.

I would see him from time to time around my house. He was a man and he lurked in the shadows. He was completely black from head to toe and his skin was charred and pock-marked, like a burnt match. I couldn’t make out his face or any other features. All I could see were his red eyes. He had the most terrifying red eyes. Even now, when I think of them, it gives me the chills.

He appeared at random and without any warning. I would be playing with my toys and all of a sudden, he would be there. He never made a sound. He never said a word. He never did anything except stand there, staring at me and smiling. Then, he would vanish as quietly and as suddenly as he had come.

As time went by, I got accustomed to his presence. It got to the point where he would appear and I would just glance at him, then go back to playing with my toys. I could always feel his eyes on me as he was standing ever so close or ever so far away.

My family knew about him, but they never saw him themselves. My mother and father thought it was cute that I had an imaginary friend, but when I described him to them, they got a little creeped out. My sister was the only one who believed he was real and she said she was scared of him.

One time, I had just finished going to the toilet and was washing my hands. I was standing on a little stool so I could reach the sink. All of a sudden, I saw the man out of the corner of my eye. He was walking up the stairs. I called my sister and told her the man was here. She came running over, but just when I was about to point at the man, he walked backwards down the stairs until he was out of sight. When she left, he came creeping back up the stairs. I gave up trying to show him to people because he clearly did not want to be seen.

Eventually, my parents moved house. I remember seeing the man with the red eyes watching as the moving van pulled away. He didn’t follow us and I didn’t see him again after that. I dismissed him as a figment of my childish imagination. Years passed and I forgot about him.

Then, one night, when I was 16 years old, I was walking upstairs to my bedroom. It was after midnight. As I was walking down the hallway, something emerged from one of the other bedrooms. It stepped out into the light and I realized, to my horror, that it was the man with the red eyes.

I stopped in my tracks and froze. My heart was in my throat. He just stood there, staring at me. The red eyes burned bright and he flashed me a malicious smile. Then, still staring at me, he slowly walked across the hallway and into my bedroom.

If this was a movie, perhaps I would have chased him down and forced him to tell me who or what he was. Perhaps it would have ended in me fighting him to the death. But this wasn’t a movie. It was real life and I did neither of these things.

I simply turned around, ran back down the stairs and fled from my house. I sat on the curb outside, shivering and shaking, until dawn arrived. I haven’t seen him again since then.

"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/shadesofred" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="SHADES OF RED"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="






Shades of Red is a scary true story about a family who move into an old house and see strange things like an unexplained red mist.

￼

It all began when we moved into the old house.

One day, my 4-year old daughter started screaming at something she had seen in the living room. She said it was a cloud of red mist that had emerged from the corner of the room. It had enveloped her and it had a horrible smell that made her sick. Then, it just disappeared.

At first, we just dismissed it, but a few days later, my wife’s sister came to visit and she brought her two little daughters. The little girls said they saw a cloud of red mist appear from the same corner and it enveloped them too.

Later that same day, my wife saw the cloud of red mist come out of the corner and wrap itself around her. She said it felt hot and suffocating and stank of burning meat.

One night, my 6-year old son heard the front door opening, so he went down to investigate. The door was open and in the doorway, he could see an odd red mist that slowly disappeared before his eyes.

At this point, I was still skeptical of all these stories. That changed on the night I fell asleep downstairs. I had a very strange dream.

In the dream, I walked into our bedroom, but it was completely different. There were no beds and it was furnished as a living room. There was a sofa and sitting on it, I saw a beautiful woman with dark red hair. She was not my wife, but in the dream, I somehow knew she was my wife.

She was crying and when she turned around and looked at me, her eyes were blackened and filled with tears. She had a look of fear on her face and when I moved towards her, she cowered as if she was being beaten.

Just then, I heard a voice behind me. It was the voice of a young boy. I turned and saw a boy standing in the doorway. He was wearing red corduroy pants and a red sweater. He was soaking wet from head to toe and his skin looked ashen and lifeless. He was not my son, but in the dream, I somehow knew he was my son.

The boy looked up at me. “Dad?” he said, a look of fear in his eyes. “Dad? Help me!”

Suddenly I woke up and found myself sitting on the sofa downstairs. My wife was sitting beside me and she screamed at me, “What was that?”

I realized that there were sounds of a struggle going on upstairs. We could hear furniture being thrown and the sound of breaking glass. I jumped off the sofa ran upstairs, but when I got to the top of the stairs, everything went silent. There was nobody there… nothing out of place… no sign of anything wrong.

All I saw was a strange red mist in the hallway. It had an iridescent glow and gradually dissipated until it disappeared. I returned downstairs to tell my wife what I had seen. We sat there in silence, unsure of what was happening and waiting for the dawn to come.

That morning, I was standing on my front porch, still trying to make sense of the dream I had. My son was playing in the garden. All of a sudden, I heard him call out. A chill ran down my spine as I heard him say, “Dad?”

I turned and looked down the hill. My son said, “Dad? Help me!” I ran over to him and saw he was digging something out of the ground. It was a strip of red corduroy material. I went to help him, but when I pulled the material away, I saw a flash of white bone underneath. I grabbed my son and ran into the house.

We called the police and when they came, they dug up the remains of a little boy. He had been buried in our garden. They said he was six years old when he died. He was wearing red corduroy pants and a red pullover.

The police are trying to locate the man who lived in the house before us. He was the father of the boy and they believe he murdered his own son, but they haven’t been able to find him. They also believe he murdered his wife, but they can’t find her body. The do have old pictures of her. She was a beautiful woman with dark red hair.
"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/blackkimono" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="THE BLACK KIMONO"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="






The Black Kimono is a scary true story about a Japanese man who has a strange encounter while staying the night in his friend’s house.

￼

I live in Japan and a lot of my friends have told me about their scary experiences with the supernatural. I guess the scariest one came from my friend, who used to be able to see ghosts when he was younger.

One day, he wanted to meet up with a girl he had gone to school with. Her name was Asako. They arranged to meet at a popular location in Tokyo. However, when the day came, he waited there for a few hours but she never showed up. Thinking she must have forgotten about it or got the day wrong, he went home.

Later that night, he called her and he found out that she was mad at him for not showing up. Apparently she had been at the meeting place at the right time, but somehow they had missed each other. Although it was strange, Tokyo is a big city and the meeting place was busy, so they laughed it off and made plans to meet at a smaller train station outside of the city.

But this time, when my friend went to meet her, he ended up waiting for a few hours. He even asked the station employees to make an announcement asking Asako to come meet him at the exit, but she never showed up. Eventually, he gave up and went home.

He called her again that night and she insisted that she had been waiting there at the exit like they had arranged. He told her how he had asked them to make an announcement and she said that she had heard it while she was standing right there at the exit, but no one else was around.

This really creeped them out, so my friend suggested that he and his girlfriend Yukiko go to Asako’s apartment to meet her that night. She agreed and my friend and Yukiko headed over right away.

When they got there, everything seemed normal. They spent the night drinking and talking and having fun. They lost track of time and before they knew it, they had missed the last train home. Asako told them they could stay overnight and pulled out a futon next to her bed for them to sleep on.

Somewhere around 3 AM, my friend woke up suddenly. He was unable to move. When he opened his eyes, he saw Asako looming over him. She was sitting on his stomach. Her eyes were black and her face was pale. Her long, black hair was hanging down in his face. She was wearing a black kimono and had a strange headdress that looked like a 3-pronged candlestick with burning candles.

As she moved closer, her hair started to blow around in a strong wind and it caught on fire. He could feel the searing heat from her blazing hair against his face, but he still couldn’t move a muscle. He began to really panic when she reached for his neck, and he tried to call out to Yukiko but his voice wouldn’t work. She started squeezing his neck, all the while whispering something that he couldn’t make out.

Suddenly, he was able to yell out and he heard someone moving on the bed. He turned to look and it was Asako, looking sleepy and confused. He looked back up at the woman strangling him and she had disappeared. His girlfriend Yukiko was lying on the floor nearby instead.

He didn’t tell them what happened so they wouldn’t get freaked out, but about a month or two later, he went to a traditional play with his girlfriend. One of the characters was the ghost of a vengeful woman who had been betrayed in her past life. Her goal was to hunt down the reincarnation of the man who betrayed her and kill him. She was pale with long, black hair and wore a black kimono. She also had a 3-pronged candlestick headdress, and her hair would catch fire from the burning candles on there.

Later on, he went to a fortune teller and asked her about it. She told him that he had betrayed a woman in his past life and that the spirit of the woman was reincarnated as Asako. When he had tried to meet up with her, his protector spirits had prevented them from seeing each other to keep him safe. However, when he went to stay in her apartment, he had trapped himself in a place where she could attack him. The fortune teller told him he was lucky to be alive.






"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="THE CUTE GUY"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="

Y


When I was in high school, I was a really naive, sheltered teenager. We lived in a really close community where there was never any crime. There was a married couple who moved in at the end of our block. They had 2 boys. One was the same age as me and the other was 2 years older.

There’s no nice way to put this. The boy who was my age was really ugly. He looked kind of like Sloth from the Goonies. However, his older brother was a really cute guy. I mean, he looked like a model.

I sat next to Sloth, the younger brother, in a few of my classes at school. I also worked on some projects with him. One day, when I was sitting beside him in class, I started making idle chit-chat with him. He looked straight into my eyes and said, “You better watch out. My older brother likes you and the last girl he liked is the reason we had to move…”

I was so shocked, I didn’t know what to say. He made it sound so grave and serious. That was all he said to me…

A few weeks later, my parents went out shopping and I was left home alone. It was night time and all of a sudden, I heard the doorbell ring. When I answered the door, there was nobody there. Then, I noticed a small envelope with my name on it sitting on the doormat. I opened it.

Well… the contents were disturbing to say the least. It was a long poem about me being attacked by a man in a cape who sneaked up on me, knocked me out with chloroform, then tied me up and brought me back to his basement where he did unspeakable things to me.

I thought it must be one of my friends pulling a prank on me. I called my friend on the phone and told her, “You got me. The poem was super creepy and really freaked me out.” She had no idea what I was talking about.

All of a sudden, while I was on the phone with her, I heard something banging against the back door of the house. It was soft at first, but it got louder and louder and kept going on and on.

Then, the banging suddenly stopped and everything was silent. I was still convinced it must be one of my friends playing a trick, so I peeked out kitchen window. I couldn’t see anyone. I was still on the phone with my friend and she was yelling at me to call the police.

Just then, the doorbell rang again. I creeped down the hall, pressed myself up to the door and peeked out the peephole. Nobody was there, but I could make out a large black lump on the front porch. I couldn’t see what it was, so I flicked the switch for the porch light, but it didn’t come on.

At this point, I was so scared, I was about to have a heart attack. My friend convinced me to hang up and call the police. A few minutes later, a squad car came by and I looked out the window.

Across the street, under a streetlamp, I could see the older brother… the cute guy. He was just standing there, smoking a cigarette and watching my house. The police went up and questioned him. Then, I saw them try to search him, but he started fighting and they had to tackle him to the ground. Eventually, they managed to put the handcuffs on him.

When they searched him, they found a lot of things… the lightbulb from my porch light, a jar of chloroform, a length of rope and a bloody knife. It was bloody because the black lump on my porch was the next door neighbor’s cat. He had killed it and carved my name in it.

The older brother was a really cute guy, but he was mentally disturbed. He was really crazy and his parents didn’t care. The younger brother had tried to warn me. I felt bad about calling him Sloth. He turned out to be one of the smartest and nicest guys in my high school. I think he gave me such a cryptic warning because he was afraid of his older brother. He was scared that his brother would find out and maybe hurt him.

I also felt terrible for the family next door and their cat that was killed.





"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="CRY IN THE NIGHT"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="








A Cry in the Night is a scary true story about a group of counselors at a summer camp who hear a voice crying out for help in the middle of the night.

This is a true story and even now, years later, I still get goosebumps thinking about it.

When I was 19 years old, I worked as a counselor in a summer camp. It was really gorgeous, with wooden cabins and a lake, but it was in the middle of nowhere. The camp was surrounded by a dense woods. There was nothing but trees and canyons and the closest town was over 20 miles away.

One night, when everyone had turned in and was sleeping soundly, I was suddenly awoken in the middle of the night. It was one of those times where you wake up and you have the feeling that something is not quite right.

My heart was racing for no apparent reason. I just lay there quietly, listening intently. The whole cabin was wooden, with fly screens over the windows, so I could hear the sound of crickets and the breeze blowing through the trees.

That’s when I heard it… a very faint cry for help. It sounded like it was coming from the woods. It was the cry of a young girl lost somewhere out in the woods.

I quickly got out of bed and woke my roommate who was another counselor. I told him to listen and when the cry came again, we both heard it. We quickly got dressed, grabbed our flashlights and hurried outside in the direction the sound was coming from.

It was intermittent, but I could clearly hear the girl’s voice saying “Help!” or “I’m lost!” quite regularly, and quite a way into the woods. She sounded like she was in a lot of distress. The quicker we found her the better, so we could get her back to camp safely.

It was dark as hell that night, and all we had to light our way were two puny flashlights. The girl was out there in the pitch black with no way of seeing anything at all.

The boys’ cabins were on one side of the lake and the girls’ were on the other. On the way, we ran into a female counselor. She had heard the cries too from her side of camp. All three of us headed into the woods together, shining our torches left and right and calling out to the lost girl.

We were reluctant to go too far into the woods because we didn’t want to get lost in the darkness. Whenever we called out to the girl and heard her respond, it sounded like she was quite far in.

After walking for about five minutes, we could hear her crying and sniffling, so we knew were were close. It sounded like she was only a few feet away and we could hear her saying “I’m scared! Where am I?” in a low voice.

We kept trying to reassure her and just when we felt we were right beside her, she suddenly went silent. “We’re here! Where are you?” we called out, but there was no answer.

Then, in the distance, we heard her voice again, crying “Help me! I’m lost! Come quick!”

We started toward the sound of her cries and just when we felt that we were right on top of her again, she went silent. We called out to her. We waited for her reply. Nothing.

Then, from even farther away, we heard her voice again: “Help! Why can’t you help me!?”

Something didn’t feel right. We all looked at each other and without a word, we decided to head back to camp. We called out to the girl and told her we were going to get help and we would come back with a search party. We could still hear faint whimpers and crying sounds from her, so we told her to sit tight and we would be back soon.

The three of us sprinted back to camp and rang the big bell at the main office to alert the whole camp that there was an emergency. The camp manager switched on the flood lights and we all met in the quad for a roll-call and a head-count.

They started by calling the names of the counselors. We were all present. Then, they called the names of the campers. All of the kids were present. Nobody was missing.

They went through the roll twice and three times. Every single person that was meant to be at the camp, was checked off and present. But what about the voice of the girl?

The camp manager and the other counselors thought it was a false alarm and said that what we had heard must have been just the echoes of our own voices. They dismissed everyone and sent us back to bed.

The three of us knew what we had heard and it wasn’t an echo. It was creepy as hell. The voice kept leading us into the woods, further and further. Someone or something was luring us deeper into the woods and to this day, I have no idea what it intended to do to us.

This was by far the creepiest thing I have ever experienced. Myself and the female counselor believed it was something paranormal, but neither of us could explain it. The counselor who was my roommate refused to talk about it, and whenever we brought it up, he would say it was just voices echoing, but when I looked in his eyes, I could see that he was scared to death. He just wanted to convince himself it didn’t happen.







"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/redbirthmark" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="RED BIRTHMARK"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="



The Red Birthmark is a creepy true story about a 3-year-old boy who solved his own murder. The story was supposedly witnessed by an Israeli doctor named Professor Eli Lasch and the boy’s story was recounted in a book about reincarnation called “Children Who Have Lived Before”.

￼

There was a 3-year old boy who lived in a village on the Golan Heights in Israel, near the border with Syria. The boy was born with a red birthmark on his forehead. As soon as he was old enough to talk, he told his family that he had lived before. He pointed to the birthmark and said he had been murdered with an axe. The boy’s parents took him to the village where he claimed he had lived. There, they met with the village elders.

The boy said he remembered his old name. It was the name of a man who had gone missing from the village 4 years before. He also showed them the house where he had lived. The boy said he remembered the name of the man who killed him. When the boy saw the man, he walked right up to him and said, “I used to be your neighbor. We had a fight and you killed me with an axe.”

The man’s face turned as white as a sheet. Then the boy told the village elders, “I even know where he buried my body.”

They followed the boy to a nearby field and he stopped in front of a pile of stones. When they removed the stones, they found a skeleton underneath. There was a wound in the skull a exactly the same place where the boy’s red birthmark was. The boy showed them where the axe was buried as well. At that point, the man broke down and confessed to the murder."
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/innocencelost" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="INNOCENCE LOST"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="







Innocence Lost is a scary true story about a 13-year old girl who falls victim to an online predator. The girl’s name is Alicia Kozakiewicz and the story is told in her own words.

￼

It was 2002 and I was 13 years old. I had dark blond hair, blue-green eyes and braces. I lived with my mom, dad and older brother in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania.

I was an average girl from an average middle class family. I was shy and wrote poetry. I was rarely in trouble.

Sometimes I would go outside with my friends to play in the park. Sometimes I would stay at home and play on the computer. I was on the computer a lot. Not just an hour a day, but hours a day.

I had a profile on Yahoo! where I posted pictures of myself. My screen name was “goddessofall” and my profile listed my interests as “witchcraft, hypnosis and mythology”. It said I wanted to be an astronaut and a model… which is a really weird combination.

￼

All I remember is starting to chat online with this person. I assumed it was a boy my age because he was interested in the same things I was… The Spice Girls and Titanic.

We chatted online for about 8 months. He always listened to me and said what I wanted to hear: “Your teacher is stupid,” or, “Why should you tidy your room when that’s your mom’s job?”

On New Year’s Day, I arranged to meet him in person for the first time. After dinner, I told my mom I was going to my room for a few minutes. I told her I would come back down for dessert. We were having apple-walnut pie. Instead, I sneaked out to finally meet my online friend in person.

I walked up maybe a block or so and I stood there for a moment. Suddenly that little voice in my head spoke up. It said: “Alicia, what are you doing? This is really stupid! You need to turn around and go back home!”

The moment I went to turn around, I heard my name being called. There was no boy there, it was a man.

The next thing I knew, I was in a car and this huge monster was squeezing my hand so tightly, I thought it was broken. He was barking commands at me: “Be good! Be quiet! The trunk’s cleaned out for you.”

I had no idea where he was taking me or what he planned to do with me.

It wasn’t until we came to the toll booths that I realized he was taking me out of state. All I could think was: “I’m so far away from home. How are my parents going to find me?”

After a 5-hour journey, he took me to his home where he pulled me down a flight of steps and kept me captive in his basement dungeon. It was full of strange torture devices, including a cage.

He kept me naked with a dog collar around my neck which was chained to a bolt in the floor. The chain was just long enough to allow me to go to the toilet.

“It’s OK to cry,” he said coldly. “This is going to be hard for you.”

The man who abducted me then starved me, beat me, tortured me and abused me. He even broadcast the abuse to his friends online. I did whatever I had to do to survive. No matter how painful, humiliating or disgusting, I did it because I wanted to live.

On the morning of the fourth day, he looked at me and said, “I’m beginning to like you too much… Tonight we’re going to go for a ride…”

“This is it,” I thought. I knew he was going to kill me. I accepted the fact that I wasn’t going to make it out of there alive.

He went off to work, leaving me alone in the basement. Lying on the floor, naked and weeping, I felt pure despair. How could I escape? I was just 13 years old.

Not long afterwards, I heard banging on the door. I heard voices screaming, “We have guns! We have guns!”

I figured he had sent people to hurt me or kill me, so I rolled underneath the bed, trying to hide. I was absolutely terrified. Just then, a man stepped around the corner and on the back of his jacket, I saw the three most beautiful letters in the alphabet…

F… B… I…

I knew then that I was safe.

Later, they told me how they had found me. On the third day of my captivity, an anonymous caller had contacted the FBI and told them he had seen a video online of me being tortured. In the video I was chained to the wall and crying. He told them he knew the kidnapper’s first name was Scott and his screen name was “master4teen_slavegirls”.

The FBI managed to trace the screen name to a Yahoo! profile. The IP address associated with the account led them to a man named Scott Tyree. He was 38 years old and was a computer programmer from Virginia.

He also had a 12-year old daughter. She had stayed at his house during the Christmas holidays. She had only gone home to her mother’s house on New Year’s Day… The same day I was abducted.

He was arrested, convicted and sentanced to 19 years in prison.

￼

After 4 days of unspeakable torture, I was reunited with my parents. I thought I’d done something wrong, that they didn’t love me anymore, but they welcomed me home with open arms. My mom said it was like I had come back from the dead. My dad couldn’t stop hugging me and said he was just glad I was alive. But I was never the same again.

I suffered from terrible flashbacks and nightmares. It was really, really difficult.

For the longest time, whenever we came to a toll booth, I would have to close my eyes and put my hands over my ears and pretend I was somewhere else.






"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/almostkidnapped" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="ALMOST KIDNAPPED"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="







Almost Kidnapped is a collection of 10 scary true stories about boys and girls who had close calls and narrowly avoided being abducted by creeps and weirdos.

￼

\n1. Who Are You?

One evening, when I was about 8 or 9, I was walking home from school. My mom worked during the day and usually came home later in the evening. When I got to my house, I took the key out of my pocket to let myself in, but just as I reached up to put the key in the lock, the door suddenly opened. My mom was standing there in her dressing gown. Instead of greeting me, she looked straight past me and, in a stern voice, demanded “Who are you?” I turned around just in time to see a man in a trenchcoat hurrying back down the path and taking off down the street. The fact that my mom was sick that day and stayed home from work probably saved me from some horrible fate…

\n2. Double Dutch

One night, my girlfriend and I were walking through the suburbs of Dublin. A truck stopped and a guy hopped. He was acting all friendly and asking for directions. He sounded Dutch. Something struck me as odd about the whole thing and it set me on edge. It seemed like he was trying to distract us. All of a sudden, out of the corner of my eye, I spotted another man. He had climbed out of the truck on the other side. He had gone all the way around the back of the truck and was trying to sneak up behind us. I quickly grabbed my girlfriend by the arm and walked straight towards the sneaky guy. He backtracked really quickly when he realized he had been seen. The first guy was all like, “Come on, we mean no harm,” but he was also talking to the other guy in Dutch. My girlfriend just started running and I followed her. We didn’t stop running until we were far away from the weird guys and their truck. That was when my girlfriend told me she understood Dutch. What they were saying to each other was, “This isn’t going to work. Let’s go.”

\n3. Facebook Kidnapping

A 12-year-old girl from Europe got a friend request on facebook. It was from one of her classmates at school. They chatted over instant messenger and he knew a lot of information about her and her school. He said he had been sick for couple of days and asked her to bring him some books he needed for homework. She was on her way to his house when she was passing a parked car on the street and the door opened. A man got out and introduced himself as her friend’s dad. He told her to get into his car and he would drive her to her friend’s house. She didn’t want to, but he insisted. Finally, he grabbed her by the hand and tried to force her into the car. However, the girl began to scream and the neighbors came out to see what it was all about. The man fled and the girl was in such a panic she forgot to look at his license plate number. It turned out later that the facebook profile had been fake. The man had followed the girl meticulously and knew everything about her. He knew where she lived, where she went to school and which of her classmates had not been at school that day.

\n4. The Man in the Truck

When I was 14, I was waiting for the bus and this pickup truck pulled up beside me. The driver kept waving at me to come closer and he held up a map. It seemed like he wanted directions. I went over to the truck and he rolled down the window. I didn’t realize what was happening until he reached out and tried to grab me by the hair. I dropped my bag and ran for it as he sped off. When I got home, I woke my mom and told her what happened. She flipped out. Then, we looked out the window. Surprise, surprise… The truck was sitting across the street and the man was sitting in the driver’s seat, staring up at us. That’s when I flipped out.

My mom called the police and gave them a description, but the man drove off. Later on, the police called back to tell us they had pulled someone over and wanted me to take a look at him. They put me in the back of an unmarked patrol car with tinted windows and drove me past a guy who was being questioned outside his truck. It was him. I almost had a panic attack. They charged him with attempted kidnapping. It made all the local newspapers. The spot where they pulled him over was right in front of an elementary school and when they searched his truck, they found rope, duct tape and an axe.

\n5. The Postman

One day, when I was 10 years old, I stayed home sick from school. I was lying on the couch, watching TV, when I heard the doorbell ringing. It was the postman. He told me he had a package to deliver, but it was so big that he needed me to help him carry. I don’t know why, but I knew something wasn’t quite right.

I didn’t see his truck parked out front and when I asked him where it was, he told me it was around the corner. I asked him why the regular postman wasn’t here and he said he was visiting family. He kept telling me to open the front door. I said I was sick and I wasn’t allowed to leave the house. I told him my parents would pick up the package from the post office, but he said that would be too much of a hassle and told me my mom would want me to take the package now.

I told him I had to get my shoes first and then i would come out and help him. Then, I closed the front door, locked it and ran to the back door and locked it too. I called our neighbor, who was a close family friend, and begged her to come over right now. Then, I stood at the front window and stared at the man. When he saw me, he yelled through the door asking if I had found my shoes yet. I yelled back, telling him that I called my neighbor to come and help carry the package because she was older and stronger. He just turned around and ran off.

They never caught him. I always wonder if he ever managed to trick some other kid.

\n6. The Tall Man in the Park

When I was 15, my mother went out shopping and left me in charge of the house. It was starting to get dark and I realized my little brother was nowhere to be found. I asked my sister if she knew where he was and she said he had gone to the park around the corner to kick his football around. I told her to watch the house while I was gone and ran off in the direction of the park.

When I got there, I was surprised to find the park completely empty. I called out my brother’s name, but there was no answer. I started to get worried. All of a sudden, I heard a faint, muffled noise coming from my left. I turned just in time to see a tall figure disappearing behind a large fence. I sprinted as fast as I could and when I came around to the other side of the fence, I saw something that almost made me choke in horror.

My little brother was being dragged down the alleyway by a tall man. I flew into a rage and tears of anger streamed down my face. I ran at him and he must have heard me coming, because he turned around to face me and dropped my younger brother. The tall man tried to grab me but I was running at him so fast that when I slammed into him, I knocked him off his feet. He swore and tried to get back up but I just started stomping on his face.

Without stopping to ask questions, I picked my brother up and ran as fast as I could back to our house. By this time, it was pitch black outside and my mother was home. She was frantic with worry and when she saw the look on both of our faces, she realized that something bad had happened. As I explained, my brother and I started crying and my mum gave us both the biggest hug ever and cried with us.

\n7. I’ll Give You a Lift

When I was 13, I was walking home from school. It was a Friday and both my parents were working and my brother was still at school. It started to rain and I had no umbrella. The next thing I knew, a car came along and slowed down.

The driver was a guy in his early thirties and he said, “Hey, Elaine, jump in. I’ll give you a lift.” I told him my name wasn’t Elaine. He apologised and said I looked very like her and offered to give me a lift anyway.

I knew this was dodgy, so I said, “No thanks, my house is just here,” and pointed to a random house nearby. Then, I quickly walked into the entrance of the house and hid there for a few minutes, waiting for him to leave.

When I walked back out, I realized he had just pulled over on the side of the road and was getting out of his car. He knew it wasn’t my house. I dropped my schoolbag and just took off running. He followed me. I ran all the way to my house when I remembered I didn’t have my keys and nobody was home. I was absolutely terrified.

I started banging on the front door and all of a sudden, it opened. My brother was standing there. He had stayed home sick from school. I was crying so much I could barely talk and I just kept pointing at the man coming up the road. My brother grabbed a Hurley stick and ran outside. As soon as the man saw my brother, he ran back to his car, jumped in and sped off.

We didn’t manage to get his licence plate number so he was never found, but I’m sure he wanted to kidnap me and possibly hurt or kill me. It was very scary and I was so lucky that my brother was there or I might have been just another statistic.

\n8. How I Lost My Finger

When I was 7, my mom asked me to deliver something to a neighbor. It was very dark that night and there were no street lights. I could barely see anything. On the way home, I came to a bend in the road with big bushes on both sides. All of a sudden, I heard a loud rustling behind me. When I looked behind me, I saw a tall, dark figure emerging from the bushes. I started running. I could hear a man’s heavy breathing close behind me. I ran as fast as I could, but he was gaining on me. I dodged to the right and took a shortcut through a hole in a row of tall bushes. I reached the driveway of ny house and heard him crash through the bushes. He was still after me.

When I got to the front door, I caught my pinky finger on the screen. I was s terrified, I rushed inside and slammed the door shut. I loced it and screamed for my parents. I didn’t notice my finger was missing until my mom gave me a big hug. My dad ran out with a gun and tried to find the guy, but he was gone. When my dad came back, he found my finger and put it in a bag of ice to take to the hospital, but they couldn’t reattach it. A few months later, in a neighboring town, a boy about my age went missing while walking home late at night. Then another went missing a few months after that. They were never heard from again and I can’t help thinking that if I hadn’t been so quick on my feet, I might have suffered the same fate.

\n9. Carjacked

One afternoon, my mother stopped by and offered to take my 3-year old daughter Jenna shopping. Jenna was reluctant to go, but I was eager for some time alone, so I encouraged her to go with her grandma.

About an hour later, my dad’s car pull up outside. As soon as he got out of his car, he yelled, “Someone stole your mother’s car and Jenna was in it.”

My mom had been waiting in line at the toy store when a man approached her and told her that her car had a flat tire. He volunteered to change it and when he was finished, my mom thanked him. He told her he was going to test the steering, but when my mom handed him the keys, he just got into the driver’s seat and sped off.

When I heard the news, I became hysterical. I couldn’t stop sobbing and I felt sick to my stomach. The police issued a bulletin alerting all officers to be on the lookout for my mother’s car and my daughter’s abduction became national news.

Over the next few hours, I was totally terrified and all I could think about was scared and lonely my daughter must be. I was worried she was going to be killed. Time passed like an eternity.

The next morning, I got a call saying they had found the car. Someone called the police to say they’d spotted an abandoned vehicle and a little girl was inside. It was Jenna. She was unharmed and still strapped into her car seat, just as she had been when the kidnapper drove away.

As soon as we got the news, we raced to the hospital where Jenna had been taken for a checkup. I ran to her and held her close. The first thing she said to me was, “I peed in Grandma’s car.”

\n10. The Creepy Old Man

My friend and I were both 9 years old and she lived just down the road from me. We always walked home from school together. One day, a car was driving very slowly along the road and the old man inside was staring at us. My friend and I felt very uneasy. All of a sudden, he pulled up right in front of us, almost hitting us. My friend ran down the path towards her house and I ran in the direction of my house. When I got to my driveway, I glanced back and saw his car. He was following me.

I was very frightened at this point and ran up to the door and banged really hard on it. At the time, my family would always argue about whose turn it was to answer the door and I knew it would take ages for them to open it. I glanced back again and saw the creepy old man walking towards me. He had gotten out of his car. I was almost crying at this point. Suddenly, my brother opened the door and when the old weirdo saw this, he jumped back into his car and tore off.

\n11. The Little Old Lady

When I was little, my mom was friends with a little old lady who lived near us. One day, the little old lady picked me up from kindergarden. She had my little brother with her and she told me my mom had sent her to pick us up. The little old lady brought us back to her house. All her furniture was covered in plastic. She gave us ice cream and let us play with some board games. After a few hours, we ate dinner and the little old lady turned on the TV. There was my mom. She was on the news, crying and freaking out and saying her children had been kidnapped. The little old lady flipped out. She called the police to tell them where we were. In the end, it turned out that my mom had completely forgotten she asked the little old lady to pick us up from school.
"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/floor" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="4TH FLOOR"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="










The 4th Floor is a true scary story about a young man who has a chilling experience when he takes an elevator in an old building and it stops on the wrong floor.

￼

One evening, I was looking for an internet cafe because I needed to send a few e-mails. I spotted one in an old building. The sign said it was on the 6th floor.

When I walked through the entrance, there was a dark hallway that led to a small elevator. I pressed the call button and when the doors opened, I stepped inside.

In a lot of Asian countries, many buildings do not have a 4th floor. The number 4 is considered bad luck because the word for “four” sounds almost the same as the word for “death”.

The buttons in the elevator were 1-2-3-5-6. I pressed the button for the 6th floor. The doors closed and the elevator quietly began to ascend.

When it stopped and the doors opened, I was about to step out when I realized that something was wrong. The hallway was in total darkness. By the light emanating from the elevator, I could make out random pieces of furniture covered with white cloth. It looked like it hasn’t been occupied for decades.

I thought I must have gotten the wrong floor, so I checked the buttons, but none of them were lit up. There was nothing to indicate which floor I was on.

Just then, I noticed something moving at the end of the darkened hallway. I couldn’t quite make out what it was, but it looked like a person dressed in some type of gown. The figure was moving slowly down the hallway, towards the elevator. It creeped me out and in a panic, I started pressing the Close Door button.

All of a sudden, the light in the elevator flickered and turned off. I was plunged into pitch darkness. I was so freaked out, I almost wet myself.

Just as I was about to lose it completely, the lights flickered and came back on. The doors closed, the elevator jolted back to life and began to ascend again. I breathed a sigh of relief.

When the doors opened this time, I was at the internet cafe. I went over to the counter and told the girl who worked there what had happened. As she listened, her face grew pale.

She said that some of the customers and a few of her co-workers had experienced something similar. She had never experienced anything herself, but she told me about the history of the building.

Apparently, the 4th floor had been a hair salon at one time. It was a prospering business until one of the women who worked there killed herself in the salon. Nobody knew the reason why, but she slit her wrists over a basin and bled to death.

The salon continued to operate, but they were plagued by weird and inexplicable events. Sometimes, when customers were having their hair washed, the water would turn as red as blood. Other people claimed that when they looked in the mirror, they would catch glimpses of a ghostly figure standing behind them. When they turned around, there would be no one there. Because of these events, the salon developed a bad reputation and began to lose customers. Eventually, they were forced to close down.

The building’s owner tried to rent the 4th floor out to other businesses, but when they found out that someone had died there, nobody would take it. Finally, the owner reduced the price to nearly nothing and it was rented by a businessman who planned to open a stationery supply store.

However, when they tried to do some renovations on the floor, there was a series of mysterious accidents. The workmen’s tools would sometimes disappear, only to be found in strange places, a large mirror suddenly shattered when nobody was near it and a workman had his hand crushed when the elevator doors closed on him unexpectedly. Eventually, the workmen were spooked and refused to continue and the businessman pulled out and left.

The building’s owner gave up trying to rent the 4th floor and just shut it down. He had the buttons in the elevator replaced and it was reprogrammed so that nobody could go to the 4th floor.

At least, that’s what was supposed to happen.

For some reason, when people took the elevator, it would sometimes stop on the 4th floor and when the doors opened, some people would see a figure coming towards them in the darkness.



"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/dangerousroads" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="DANGEROUS ROADS"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="




Desert Roads is a colection of scary true stories about people who are driving through lonely or deserted areas and come across something truly frightening.

￼


\n1. California Desert

I was driving through the California desert, on my way to New Mexico. Taking a shortcut, I found myself all alone on a two lane road driving through the desolate landscape. There was nothing for miles, except for an abandoned ghost town. At the time, I had heard rumors that the area was a hotspot for satanic group activity.

It was late in the evening and the sun was setting. Soon it would be dark. I was driving through a canyon with high grass on both sides of the road. Up ahead, I noticed something in the middle of the road, blocking my path. As I came closer, I slowed down to a crawl.

There was a truck stopped sideways across both lanes. On the road, there was an open suitcase and clothes were scattered everywhere. Two bodies lay face-down in the road. It was a man and a woman and they appeared to be dead.

I stopped a hundred feet or so from the scene of the accident. The hair on the back of my neck was standing up. Something was very wrong, but I couldn’t put my finger on exactly what it was.

I reached into the back seat and pulled out my rifle, putting a round into the chamber. Then it hit me. The scene of the accident looked too perfect. It was as if it had been staged.

Was it some sort of ambush or was I just being paranoid?

I broke out into a cold sweat. My heart was pounding in my chest. Something was seriously wrong. I didn’t dare to get out of the car.

As I scanned the road, I saw a line I could drive. I could pass the body of the man lying in the road on the left, then swerve to the right side and pass the body of the woman. I dropped into first gear, punched the engine and drove the line I planned.

I passed the back of the truck without hitting it or either of the bodies in the road. I continued forward a few hundred feet and then slowed down so I could breathe and let my heart slow down.

As I looked in the rearview mirror, I suddenly realized that the two bodies had gotten up to their knees and at least twenty shadowy figures were emerging from the tall grass on either side of the road.

At that moment, I began to panic. My right foot stepped on the gas and I sped off down the road. I didn’t let up until I had to slow down until I reached the highway.

I will never know what would have happened to me had I gotten out of the car to check on the bodies or if I had stopped my car closer to them. Somehow I don’t think it would have been good.

Sometimes real life can be scarier than any horror movie.


\n2. Baby in the Road

One night, my friend was out driving in his truck in the Maine countryside. It was a remote area where you could drive for hours without seeing civilization. There were just trees and more trees that stretched on for miles. He was driving along when he suddnely saw something in the road up ahead. He stopped the car to take a look, but he couldn’t quite make it out. Whatever it was, it was moving. It was moving very, very slowly. He got curious, so he drove closer to it in his truck. It was a baby, lying in the middle of the road. He was stunned, thinking someone had just abandoned a baby in the middle of the road. He got out of the truck and walked over to it. When he went to pick it up, he realized that it wasn’t a baby at all. It was a baby doll and it was being slowly dragged across the road by a string. He ran back to his truck and drove out of there fast as he could.


\n3. Back Roads

Back roads are scary at night. A few years ago, I was driving down a lonely country back road. It was around 2 AM and there was no cell phone reception in the area. I slowed down as I was rounding a curve and all of a sudden, I saw a car sitting in the middle of the road. There were no lights on and the driver’s door was standing open. I stopped my car and turned on the high beams to see if everything was OK. Just then, I noticed 2 men coming out of the woods behind my car. They were crouching down and approaching the back doors on both sides. I slammed the gas and as I took off, I almost side-swiped the car they left in the middle of the road. It was so dark that if they had come out of the woods a couple more feet behind my car, I probably would never even have noticed them…


\n4. Jason Mask

I was driving home after a long day work when I saw a dark figure in the road up ahead. There were no houses around, no cars, nothing. As I got closer, I could tell it was a man in a black trench coat standing in the middle of the road. I slowed down because I was afraid I was going to hit him. Coming a little bit closer, I could see he was wearing a hockey mask. It looked exactly like Jason Voorhees from the Friday the 13th movies. The man jumped out in front of my car in an attempt to make me stop. It scared the hell out of me. I managed to swerve and drove around him. I still don’t know if he was out to harm me or if he was just messing with cars that went by. I’ll never forget looking out of my window and seeing that Jason mask staring back at me!





"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/yellowraincoat" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="THE YELLOW RAINCOAT"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="








The Yellow Raincoat is a scary true story about a young Korean woman who has a frightening encounter on an elevator. It is based on a supposedly true story told by a user named Whale Baboon.

￼

My mom’s friend is a woman who lives in South Korea. This happened 10 years ago. She lived with her husband and her young daughter in an apartment building in Seoul. At the time, her husband was always at work during the day and her daughter was very young, so she was a stay-at-home mother.

One day, the woman went out to run some errands and she took her daughter with her. When they came back, they stood in the lobby of the apartment building and pressed the button for the elevator.

When it arrived and the doors opened, she saw that there was a man already in the elevator. He was wearing a yellow raincoat and he also had a yellow hat on his head.

The woman got onto the elevator with her daughter and she pressed the button for her floor. Something about the man made her feel uneasy. He never looked up at her. He just kept staring at the floor. It was as if he was keeping his head down so she couldn’t really see his face.

As the doors closed and the elevator began to ascend, the woman glanced at the man out of the corner of her eye. She noticed that he was carrying something close to his side. Something that was wrapped in newspaper.

The man was making her nervous. Something about him wasn’t right, but she couldn’t put her finger on what it was. She made her daughter stand on the other side of her. She didn’t know why, but she wanted to place herself in between the man and her daughter.

There was an uncomfortable silence as the elevator slowly went up, floor by floor. The woman glanced at the elevator buttons and noticed that only one button was lit up. It was the button for her floor. None of the other numbers had been pressed.

Things started to click in her head. That’s when she realized what it was about the man that was making her so nervous. He was wearing a raincoat, but it wasn’t raining outside. The sun had been shining all day.

The woman started to panic. She took out her cell phone and, even though her husband was at work, she pretended she was calling him. She started saying things like, “I’m on the elevator and about to get off. Can you open the front door for me?” and making it seem like her husband was waiting at home for her.

When the elevator reached her floor and the doors opened, she quickly grabbed her daughter by the hand and got off. She started to walk as fast as she could, down the hallway to her apartment.

Glancing back, she noticed that the man had also gotten off the elevator on her floor and was slowly following her down the hallway. When she got to her apartment, she started to bang on the door and said loudly, “Hey, I’m home! Open the door!” She even tried to make it seem as if her husband was coming to answer the door.

When the man in the yellow raincoat saw this, he stopped in his tracks, turned around and started to walk back towards the elevator. She watched him until he got back on the elevator and then she breathed a sigh of relief.

She started to punch in the keycode to open her door, but her hands were shaking so much, she kept hitting the wrong numbers. Each time she pushed a button, it made a beeping sound.

To her horror, she realized that the elevator doors hadn’t closed. The man in the yellow raincoat was still there.
He could hear the beeps. That meant he knew that no one was going to answer the door for her.

She saw him get out of the elevator and come running down the hallway towards her.

The woman let out a scream.

She tried one more time and managed to punch in the correct keycode. The door opened and she pushed her daughter inside. She jumped through the doorway herslef and when she turned around, she saw that the man in the yellow raincoat was right behind her.

She just managed to slam the door in his face before he could wedge his hand into the doorway to block her. Her heart was thumping in her chest as she quickly locked the front door and peered through the peephole. She saw the man in the yellow raincoat standing at the door with a knife in his hand.

As she watched, he stood there for a moment, then calmly turned and walked back towards the elevator.

A few months later, the woman was watching television when a newsflash came on. It said that police had captured a serial killer named Yoo Young Chul. He was responsible for the murders of over 20 young women and old men. After he killed them, he mutilated their bodies and ate parts of them.

The woman told my mom that she could never forget the dread she felt when she saw the footage on the news of the serial killer being led away by police. He was still wearing the same yellow raincoat.


"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/blackstone" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="THE BLACK STONE"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="
The Black Stone is a true scary story about some young boys who explore an old abandoned graveyard in the wilderness. It is based on an experience from a user named Efflux.

￼

When I was young, my parents rented a cabin in the woods. We would go there on weekends to spend some time in the wilderness. My brothers and I loved to explore.

There was a dirt road that ran past the cabin and at the end of the road, there was a small graveyard. It was surrounded by a wrought iron fence with spikes on the top. The gate was locked with a rusty chain and padlock, but we were able to pull the bars apart and squeeze through.

The gravestones were very old and worn. On top of one of the graves, there was a smooth black stone. It looked like onyx and when we were leaving, my older brother took it and put it in his pocket.

That night, we were sleeping in the cabin. My parents slept in the bedroom and my brothers and I slept in the living room. All of a sudden, in the middle of the night, we heard a loud banging at the front door.

BANG! BANG! BANG!

We were scared out of our wits.

BANG! BANG! BANG!

The door was shaking. It sounded like someone was trying to knock it off the hinges. My dad emerged from the bedroom and asked what was going on.

BANG! BANG! BANG!

When he saw the looks on our faces, he knew we had no idea.

BANG! BANG! BANG!

My dad grabbed an axe and walked over to the door. He looked just as scared as we were. He raised the axe and opened the door, but there was nothing out there. The banging had stopped and the night was black and silent.

After we calmed down, we went back to bed, but none of us were able to get much sleep. The next day, when we went back to the graveyard, the smooth black stone that my brother had taken was sitting on top of the same grave. As soon as we saw that, we ran away and never went back.
"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="15dp" />

        <ImageView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:src="@drawable/manintheattic" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="MAN IN THE ATTIC"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light"
            android:textSize="30dp"
            android:textStyle="bold" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="The Man in the Attic is a true scary story about a woman who hears strange noises at night that seem to be coming from overhead. As time goes by she comes to believe that there is a ghost in the house. This is also known as the “Jackie Hernandez Haunting” and “The San edro Poltergeist”. It was featured in an episode of the TV show Paranormal Witness.

￼

There was a woman named Jackie lived in a rented bungalow house with her 2-year old son Jamie and her baby daughter Samantha. About a month after she moved in, she began hearing strange noises. It sounded as if they were coming from the attic. She tried to ignore them, but every time she heard the unexplained noises, it sent a chill down her spine.

One night, she noticed that the trap door that led to the attic was hanging open. She had never opened it and had no idea what was up the attic. She was too scared to go up and investigate, so she just closed the trap door again. She had the strangest feeling that she was not alone in the house.

Jackie hired a 16-year-old girl named Tina to babysit her children. One day, when they were in the kitchen, they noticed weird glowing lights floating around near the trap door in the ceiling. Jackie grabbed her camera and told the babysitter to take some pictures. As soon as Tina looked through the camera lens, she saw something that terrified her. She screamed in horror and dropped the camera and both of them ran out of the house in fear for their lives. The babysitter said what she had seen was the ghostly image of an old man with a face that looked like a skeleton.

One day, she went shopping. When she came home, she walked into the kitchen and found something creepy on the refrigerator. The magnetic letters of the alphabet on the fridge door had been rearranged to read, “GET THE HELL OUT”. It unnerved her so much that she couldn’t sleep and she spent the night awake, watching over her children.
In the middle of the night, she heard what sounded like loud breathing. She went down the hallway, looking for the source of the noise. When she opened the door to the spare bedroom, she recoiled in horror. What she saw was an old man sitting on her son’s bed. Jackie was so terrified that she grabbed her kids and ran out of the house. She couldn’t afford to move out of the house and she was worried that if she told anyone what was going on, they would think she was out of her mind.

The next day, she was in the kitchen, washing the dishes and she noticed that her rubber gloves were covered in blood. She pulled off the gloves, but there were no cuts on her hands. Then, she looked around and saw blood pouring down the kitchen walls. That night, Jackie woke up in the middle of the night and felt someone holding her down. She couldn’t get up and she couldn’t breathe. She thought she was going to die. Suddenly, it let her go. She grabbed her kids and ran out of the house.

That was the last straw. She couldn’t take it anymore. She called in a team of paranormal investigators and asked them to find out what was going on in her house.

The next evening, the investigators arrived with their equiptment. They set up cameras all over the house and Jackie told them all of the supernatural events she had experienced. All of a sudden, the lights went out. They suspected that whoever or whatever was haunting the house, it was angry that the investigators were there.

When the lights came back on, one of the investigators decided to go up into the attic and take some pictures. He climbed up through the trap door and the rest ofthe team waited for him to come back down.

All of a sudden, they heard a scream coming from the attic. The investigator fell through the trap door and claimed that something had grabbed his camera. Just then, they heard the sound of someone walking around in the attic, even though there was nobody up there. The investigators recovered their camera and left.

Two other investigators decided to go up into the attic with a flashlight and another camera. The rest of the team waited in the kitchen. All of a sudden, the heard a loud SNAP! and the investigators in the attic started yelling and screaming. When they came back down, one of them was choking and gasping for air and he had red marks around his throat. They said something had attacked them in the attic.

When they looked at the pictures on the camera, they were horrified by what they found. In one picture, one of the investigators had an old rope around his neck like a noose and he looked like he was being choked. Jackie and the team of investigators ran out of the house screaming.

After that, Jackie refused to spend another night in the house. She gathered her children and moved out. Since then, the house has been rented to other people, but none of them stay very long. To this day, everyone involved in the case is still haunted by what happened in the attic.

The scariest thing about this story is that it is true. It happened in San Pedro, California in 1989 and the woman’s name was Jackie Hernandez.


"
            android:textColor="@android:color/holo_red_light" />

        <TextView
            android:layout_width="wrap_content"
            android:layout_height="wrap_content"
            android:text="STORY CREDITS :- www.scaryforkids.com"
            android:textColor="@color/colorPrimaryDark"
            android:textSize="5dp" />
    </LinearLayout>
</ScrollView>